Corporate O
America B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Anne B-PER
Murray I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

Corporate O
America B-LOC

firm O
Towers B-ORG
Perrin I-ORG

said O
Sandra B-PER
O'Neal I-PER
Perrin I-ORG

a O
Towers B-ORG
Perrin I-ORG

said O
O'Neal B-PER

, O
O'Neal B-PER

After O
World B-MISC
War I-MISC
II I-MISC

, O
O'Neal B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
O'Neal B-PER

said O
O'Neal B-PER

, O
O'Neal B-PER

, O
O'Neal B-PER

- O
FIORENTINA B-ORG
DOUBLE O

WITH O
BATISTUTA B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
MILAN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Argentine B-MISC
Batistuta I-PER

striker O
Gabriel B-PER
Batistuta I-PER
the O

gave O
Fiorentina B-ORG
Cup I-MISC

the O
Italian B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
victory O

2-1 O
Supercup B-MISC
A I-MISC

over O
serie B-MISC
A I-MISC
. O

champions O
Milan B-ORG

the O
Florence B-LOC
winners O

the O
Cup B-MISC
winners O

the O
Cup B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Batistuta B-PER
the O

gave O
Fiorentina B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Sweden B-LOC
Schwarz I-PER

's O
Stefan B-PER
Schwarz I-PER
did O

and O
Batistuta B-PER
Baresi I-PER

defender O
Franco B-PER
Baresi I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Montenegrin B-MISC
Savicevic I-PER

midfielder O
Dejan B-PER
Savicevic I-PER
goalkeeper O

young O
Fiorentina B-ORG
Toldo I-PER

goalkeeper O
Francesco B-PER
Toldo I-PER

, O
Batistuta B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
French B-MISC
Desailly I-PER

midfielder O
Marcel B-PER
Desailly I-PER
, O

the O
Argentine B-MISC
Juniors I-ORG

at O
Boca B-ORG
Juniors I-ORG
in O

joined O
Fiorentina B-ORG
coach O

new O
Milan B-ORG
Tabarez I-PER

coach O
Oscar B-PER
Tabarez I-PER
rammed O

and O
Batistuta B-PER

dubbed O
Batigol B-PER
fans O

adoring O
Fiorentina B-ORG
who O

for O
Fiorentina B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Milan B-ORG
Weah I-PER

year O
George B-PER
Weah I-PER
team O

while O
Italian B-MISC
Baggio I-PER

mate O
Roberto B-PER
Baggio I-PER

New O
Dutch B-MISC
Davids I-PER

signing O
Edgar B-PER
Davids I-PER
substitute O

a O
Milan B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Libyan B-MISC
. O

in O
Malta B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
VALLETTA B-LOC

A O
Libyan B-MISC
, O

in O
Malta B-LOC

of O
Amer B-PER
Hishem I-PER
Ali I-PER
Mohammed I-PER
, O

in O
Sliema B-LOC
, O

from O
Valletta B-LOC

Commissioner O
George B-PER
Grech I-PER
had O

that O
Mohammed B-PER
militant O

an O
Islamic B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SUGO B-LOC
1996-08-25 O

, O
Japan B-LOC

1. O
Yuuchi B-PER
Takeda I-PER
) O

( O
Japan B-LOC
38 O

) O
Honda B-ORG

5. O
John B-PER
Kocinski I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
38:36.306 O

) O
Ducati B-ORG

6. O
Aaron B-PER
Slight I-PER
Zealand I-LOC

) O
Honda B-ORG

) O
Honda B-ORG

9. O
Akira B-PER
Ryo I-PER
) O

) O
Kawasaki B-ORG

10. O
Shiya B-PER
Takeishi I-PER
) O

( O
Japan B-LOC
38:52.271 O

) O
Kawasaki B-ORG

: O
Haga B-PER

) O
Honda B-ORG

3. O
Haga B-PER

4. O
Slight B-PER

6. O
Fujiwara B-PER

7. O
Ryo B-PER

8. O
Takeishi B-PER

9. O
Yoshikawa B-PER

10. O
Corser B-PER

: O
Aoki B-PER

1. O
Slight B-PER

6. O
Pier B-PER
Francesco I-PER
Chili I-PER
) O

( O
Italy B-LOC
175 O

) O
Ducati B-ORG

7. O
Simon B-PER
Crafar I-PER
Zealand I-LOC

9. O
Yoshikawa B-PER

10. O
Neil B-PER
Hodgson I-PER
) O

( O
Britain B-LOC
82 O

) O
Ducati B-ORG

of O
Japanese B-MISC
Haga I-PER

rider O
Noriyuki B-PER
Haga I-PER

) O
Honda B-ORG

3. O
Slight B-PER

5. O
Fujiwara B-PER

9. O
Corser B-PER

10. O
Keiichi B-PER
Kitigawa I-PER
) O

( O
Japan B-LOC
38:42.333 O

) O
Suzuki B-ORG

: O
Aoki B-PER

1. O
Slight B-PER

6. O
Pier B-PER
Francesco I-PER
Chili I-PER
) O

( O
Italy B-LOC
175 O

) O
Ducati B-ORG

7. O
Simon B-PER
Crafar I-PER
Zealand I-LOC

9. O
Yoshikawa B-PER

10. O
Neil B-PER
Hodgson I-PER
) O

( O
Britain B-LOC
82 O

) O
Ducati B-ORG

- O
MAJOR B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

of O
Major B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
American B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BOSTON B-ORG
5 O

8 O
Seattle B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CLEVELAND B-ORG
5 O

8 O
Milwaukee B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
California B-ORG
0 O

13 O
BALTIMORE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Oakland B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

6 O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-ORG
9 O

10 O
Toronto B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Texas B-ORG
2 O

13 O
MINNESOTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Detroit B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

7 O
KANSAS B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

- O
TOGO B-LOC
1-0 O

BEAT O
CONGO B-LOC
NATIONS I-MISC

IN O
AFRICA B-MISC
NATIONS I-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LOME B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Togo B-LOC
1-0 O

beat O
Congo B-LOC

their O
African B-MISC
Nations I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

: O
Salou B-PER
Bachirou I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Togo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Iran B-LOC
of O

accuses O
Iraq B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
NICOSIA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Iran B-LOC
Nations I-ORG

the O
United B-ORG
Nations I-ORG
Takht I-PER

, O
Majid B-PER
Takht I-PER
Ravanchi I-PER
Secretary-General O

to O
U.N. B-ORG
Boutros-Ghali I-PER

a O
U.N.-sponsored B-MISC

- O
FERRIGATO B-PER
CUP I-MISC

STRAIGHT O
WORLD B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ZURICH B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Andrea B-PER
Ferrigato I-PER
sprinted O

of O
Italy B-LOC
Cup I-MISC

cycling O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
Grand O

the O
Swiss B-MISC
on O

Grand O
Prix B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ferrigato B-PER
Classic I-MISC

the O
Leeds B-MISC
Classic I-MISC
's O

over O
Britain B-LOC
Sciandri I-PER

's O
Max B-PER
Sciandri I-PER

26-year-old O
Italian B-MISC
Bartoli I-PER

compatriot O
Michele B-PER
Bartoli I-PER
Cup I-MISC

defending O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
Museeuw I-PER

champion O
Johan B-PER
Museeuw I-PER
in O

of O
Belgium B-LOC

champion O
Lance B-PER
Armstrong I-PER
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
velodrome O

the O
Oerlikon B-LOC

vault O
Ferrigato B-PER
Cup I-MISC

overall O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
continues O

but O
Museeuw B-PER

- O
MAJOR B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Major B-MISC
League I-MISC
Baseball I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
AMERICAN B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BALTIMORE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BOSTON B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
TORONTO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
DETROIT B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CENTRAL B-MISC
DIVISION I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
CLEVELAND B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
MINNESOTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
MILWAUKEE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
KANSAS B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
WESTERN B-MISC
DIVISION I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
TEXAS B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SEATTLE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
OAKLAND B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CALIFORNIA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SEATTLE B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
BOSTON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MILWAUKEE B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
CLEVELAND B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
CALIFORNIA B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
BALTIMORE B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
TORONTO B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
CHICAGO B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
OAKLAND B-ORG
YORK I-LOC

AT O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
DETROIT B-ORG
CITY I-LOC

AT O
KANSAS B-LOC
CITY I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
TEXAS B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
MINNESOTA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
NATIONAL B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ATLANTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
MONTREAL B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
FLORIDA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PHILADELPHIA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CENTRAL B-MISC
DIVISION I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ST B-ORG
LOUIS I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
HOUSTON B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CINCINNATI B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PITTSBURGH B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
WESTERN B-MISC
DIVISION I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SAN B-ORG
DIEGO I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LOS B-ORG
ANGELES I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
COLORADO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SAN B-ORG
FRANCISCO I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
ATLANTA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
ST B-ORG
LOUIS I-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
HOUSTON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG
ANGELES I-LOC

AT O
LOS B-LOC
ANGELES I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MONTREAL B-ORG
FRANCISCO I-LOC

AT O
SAN B-LOC
FRANCISCO I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
CINCINNATI B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
FLORIDA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
PITTSBURGH B-ORG
END_TAG O

AT O
COLORADO B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
PHILADELPHIA B-ORG
DIEGO I-LOC

AT O
SAN B-LOC
DIEGO I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Zenith B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Susan B-PER
Nadeau I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-LOC

and O
The B-ORG
Walt I-ORG
Disney I-ORG
Co I-ORG

with O
Zenith B-ORG

to O
Zenith B-ORG

, O
William B-PER
Luehrs I-PER
, O

the O
Glenview B-LOC
company O

, O
Ill.-based B-MISC
Services I-ORG

's O
Networks B-ORG
Services I-ORG
Division I-ORG

, O
Zenith B-ORG
York I-ORG

the O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Stock I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG

called O
Americast B-ORG

to O
Disney B-ORG
's O

, O
Americast B-ORG
Corp. I-ORG

companies O
Ameritech B-ORG
Corp. I-ORG
Corp. I-ORG

, O
BellSouth B-ORG
Corp. I-ORG
Corp. I-ORG

, O
GTE B-ORG
Corp. I-ORG
Communications I-ORG

and O
SBC B-ORG
Communications I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Americast B-ORG
New I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Zenith B-ORG
, O

in O
Woodridge B-LOC
. O

, O
Ill B-LOC

, O
Zenith B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Luehrs B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Zenith B-ORG
, O

its O
Chihuahua B-LOC
, O

, O
Mexico B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Luehrs B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Americast B-ORG

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Luehrs B-PER

strong O
Zenith B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Zenith B-ORG

, O
South B-MISC
Korea-based I-MISC
Electronics I-ORG

Korea-based I-MISC
LG B-ORG
Electronics I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
. O

in O
Zenith B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Robert B-PER
Gutenstein I-PER
, I-ORG

for O
Kalf B-ORG
, I-ORG
Voorhis I-ORG
& I-ORG
Co I-ORG

ONE O
ROMANIAN B-MISC
. O

IN O
BULGARIA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SOFIA B-LOC

One O
Romanian B-MISC
bus O

a O
Romanian-registered B-MISC
one O

a O
Bulgarian B-MISC
, O

northern O
Bulgaria B-LOC

of O
Rousse B-LOC
Tarnovo I-LOC

and O
Veliko B-LOC
Tarnovo I-LOC

A O
Romanian B-MISC
Marco I-PER

woman O
Maria B-PER
Marco I-PER

-- O
Sofia B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

- O
ENGLAND B-LOC
FINAL O

V O
PAKISTAN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

between O
England B-LOC
at O

and O
Pakistan B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC
Crawley I-PER

( O
J. B-PER
Crawley I-PER
Thorpe I-PER

, O
G. B-PER
Thorpe I-PER
END_TAG O

; O
Waqar B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Pakistan B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Saeed B-PER
Anwar I-PER
b O

c O
Croft B-PER
176 O

b O
Cork B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Aamir B-PER
Sohail I-PER
b O

c O
Cork B-PER
46 O

b O
Croft B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ijaz B-PER
Ahmed I-PER
b O

c O
Stewart B-PER
61 O

b O
Mullally B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Inzamam-ul-Haq B-PER
b O

c O
Hussain B-PER
35 O

b O
Mullally B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Salim B-PER
Malik I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Asif B-PER
Mujtaba I-PER

: O
Wasim B-PER
Akram I-PER
Khan I-PER

, O
Moin B-PER
Khan I-PER
Ahmed I-PER

, O
Mushtaq B-PER
Ahmed I-PER
Younis I-PER

, O
Waqar B-PER
Younis I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Mohammad B-PER
Akam I-PER

: O
Lewis B-PER
22-6-56-2 O

, O
Mullally B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Croft B-PER
14.3-4-45-1 O

, O
Cork B-PER
17-0-91-0 O

, O
Salisbury B-PER

INJURED O
CHANDA B-PER
RUBIN I-PER
OPEN I-MISC

OF O
U.S. B-MISC
OPEN I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

10th-ranked O
American B-MISC
Rubin I-PER

American B-MISC
Chanda B-PER
Rubin I-PER
Open I-MISC

the O
U.S. B-MISC
Open I-MISC
Tennis I-MISC
Championships I-MISC

20-year-old O
Rubin B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Rubin B-PER
champion O

eighth-seeded O
Olympic B-MISC
Davenport I-PER

champion O
Lindsay B-PER
Davenport I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Davenport B-PER
Habsudova I-PER

17th-ranked O
Karina B-PER
Habsudova I-PER
. O

of O
Slovakia B-LOC

, O
Habsudova B-PER
's O

into O
Rubin B-PER
will O

while O
Davenport B-PER
Tennis I-MISC

to O
U.S. B-MISC
Tennis I-MISC
Association I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Rubin B-PER
Open I-MISC

former O
Australian B-MISC
Open I-MISC
Pierce I-PER

champion O
Mary B-PER
Pierce I-PER
semifinalist O

20th-ranked O
Wimbledon B-MISC
McGrath I-PER

semifinalist O
Meredith B-PER
McGrath I-PER

's O
Australian B-MISC
Open I-MISC
Becker I-PER

champion O
Boris B-PER
Becker I-PER
Slam I-MISC

final O
Grand B-MISC
Slam I-MISC

- O
EUROPEAN B-MISC
CUP I-MISC
, O

FOR O
AEK B-ORG
, O

, O
OLYMPIAKOS B-ORG
. O

, O
PAO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
ATHENS B-LOC

the O
European B-MISC

the O
UEFA B-ORG
END_TAG O

involving O
Greek B-MISC

in O
Geneva B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
x-AEK B-ORG
Athens I-ORG
) O

( O
Greece B-LOC
Humenne I-ORG

v O
Chemlon B-ORG
Humenne I-ORG
) O

( O
Slovakia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
x-Olympiakos B-ORG
( O

v O
Ferencvaros B-ORG
) O

( O
Hungary B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
x-PAO B-ORG
Warsaw I-ORG

v O
Legia B-ORG
Warsaw I-ORG
) O

( O
Poland B-LOC

-- O
Dimitris B-PER
Kontogiannis I-PER
Newsroom I-ORG

, O
Athens B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Israeli B-MISC
to O

invites O
Arafat B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
JERUSALEM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israeli B-MISC
Weizman I-PER

President O
Ezer B-PER
Weizman I-PER
Arafat I-PER

invited O
Yasser B-PER
Arafat I-PER
's O

, O
Israel B-LOC

The O
Yedioth B-ORG
Ahronoth I-ORG
Netanyahu I-PER

Minister O
Benjamin B-PER
Netanyahu I-PER
president O

the O
Palestinian B-MISC

said O
Weizman B-PER
village O

central O
Israeli B-MISC
after O

of O
Caesarea B-LOC
sent O

after O
Arafat B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Netanyahu B-PER
last O

met O
Weizman B-PER
said O

, O
Yedioth B-ORG

meet O
Arafat B-PER
as O

quoted O
Weizman B-PER
. O

telling O
Netanyahu B-PER

said O
Netanyahu B-PER
an O

give O
Weizman B-PER

of O
Israeli B-MISC

But O
Weizman B-PER
's O

of O
Israel B-LOC
, O

with O
Egypt B-LOC
-- O

the O
Palestinians B-MISC
government O

former O
Labour B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Nepal B-LOC
. O

to O
China B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
KATHMANDU B-LOC

King O
Birendra B-PER
on O

left O
Nepal B-LOC
, O

to O
China B-LOC

visited O
China B-LOC
President O

meet O
Chinese B-MISC
Zemin I-PER

President O
Jiang B-PER
Zemin I-PER
Peng I-PER

Premier O
Li B-PER
Peng I-PER

Minister O
Prakash B-PER
Chandra I-PER
Lohani I-PER
leaders O

with O
Chinese B-MISC

The O
Himalayan B-MISC
and O

between O
China B-LOC
, O

and O
India B-LOC

Queen O
Aishwarya B-PER
capital O

the O
Tibetan B-MISC
. O

of O
Lhasa B-LOC

visit O
Chongqing B-LOC
capital O

the O
Chinese B-MISC
, O

, O
Beijing B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
HK B-LOC
to O

's O
Tsang B-PER
, O

visit O
Indonesia B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC

, O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
HONG B-LOC
KONG I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC
Tsang I-PER

Secretary O
Donald B-PER
Tsang I-PER
and O

visit O
Indonesia B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC

and O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC

In O
Jakarta B-LOC
will O

, O
Tsang B-PER
, O

President O
Suharto B-PER
Mar'ie B-PER

of O
Finance B-ORG
Muhammad I-PER

Finance B-ORG
Mar'ie B-PER
Muhammad I-PER
Affairs I-ORG

of O
Foreign B-ORG
Affairs I-ORG
Alatas I-PER

Affairs I-ORG
Ali B-PER
Alatas I-PER
and I-ORG

of O
Trade B-ORG
and I-ORG
Industry I-ORG
Ariwibowo I-PER

Industry I-ORG
Tungky B-PER
Ariwibowo I-PER

his O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
will O

, O
Tsang B-PER
Bolger I-PER

Minister O
Jim B-PER
Bolger I-PER
McKinnon I-PER

Minister O
Don B-PER
McKinnon I-PER
Bill B-PER

of O
Finance B-ORG
Birch I-PER

Finance B-ORG
Bill B-PER
Birch I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Grozny B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
ALKHAN-YURT B-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
Russia B-LOC

of O
Grozny B-LOC
planes O

by O
Russian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG
Sheets I-PER

correspondent O
Lawrence B-PER
Sheets I-PER
, O

of O
Alkhan-Yurt B-LOC
since O

from O
Grozny B-LOC
security O

of O
Russian B-MISC
Lebed I-PER

chief O
Alexander B-PER
Lebed I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Lebed B-PER
separatists O

with O
Chechen B-MISC
, O

on O
Grozny B-LOC

-- O
Algeria B-ORG
TV I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PARIS B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Algerian B-MISC
guerrillas O

three O
Moslem B-MISC
bishop O

leading O
French B-MISC
, O

western O
Algeria B-LOC
state-run O

the O
Algerian B-MISC

slain O
Moslem B-MISC

the O
French B-MISC
Bishop O

Roman O
Catholic B-MISC
Claverie I-PER

Bishop O
Pierre B-PER
Claverie I-PER

- O
S.AFRICAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
JOHANNESBURG B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC

MON O
Gencor B-ORG

MON O
Gencor B-ORG

MON O
Primedia B-ORG

MON O
Primedia B-ORG

MON O
Distillers B-ORG

MON O
Distillers B-ORG

TUE O
Iscor B-ORG

TUE O
Iscor B-ORG

TUE O
McCarthy B-ORG

TUE O
McCarthy B-ORG

WED O
Imphold B-ORG

WED O
Imphold B-ORG

THU O
M&R B-ORG

THU O
M&R B-ORG

THU O
JD B-ORG
Group I-ORG

THU O
JD B-ORG
Group I-ORG

-- O
Johannesburg B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

of O
Crohn B-PER

four O
Swedish B-MISC
's O

of O
Crohn B-PER

Dr O
Andrew B-PER
Wakefield I-PER
Free I-LOC

the O
Royal B-LOC
Free I-LOC
Hospital I-LOC
School I-LOC
of I-LOC
Medicine I-LOC
Hospital I-LOC

at O
University B-LOC
Hospital I-LOC
, O

, O
Uppsala B-LOC

had O
Crohn B-PER
's O

, O
Wakefield B-PER
medical O

the O
Lancet B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Crohn B-PER

( O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Wis B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-LOC

, O
Wisconsin B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Tommy B-PER
Thompson I-PER

, O
Wisconsin B-LOC
Department I-ORG

President O
Bill B-PER
Clinton I-PER

, O
Wisconsin B-LOC
said O

, O
Thompson B-PER

dubbed O
W-2 B-MISC

, O
Wisconsin B-LOC

-- O
Karen B-PER
Pierog I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Polish B-MISC
. O

in O
Libya B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
TUNIS B-LOC

A O
Polish B-MISC
tabloid O

a O
Polish B-MISC
was O

that O
Libya B-LOC
nurses O

100 O
Polish B-MISC
African I-MISC

the O
North B-MISC
African I-MISC

in O
Libya B-LOC
embassy O

the O
Polish B-MISC
, O

in O
Tripoli B-LOC
Awdankiewicz I-PER

, O
Tadeusz B-PER
Awdankiewicz I-PER
by O

told O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Poland B-LOC
to O

to O
Libya B-LOC
said O

but O
Awdankiewicz B-PER

800 O
Polish B-MISC
. O

in O
Libya B-LOC

- O
Royal B-ORG
Oak I-ORG

-- O
EVEREN B-ORG
Securities I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
Oak I-ORG

of O
Royal B-ORG
Oak I-ORG
Mines I-ORG
Inc I-ORG

of O
Royal B-ORG
Oak I-ORG
said O

, O
EVEREN B-ORG

-- O
Royal B-ORG
Oak I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG
Chicago I-ORG
Newsdesk I-ORG

- O
ENGLAND B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC
at O

against O
Pakistan B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ka B-ORG
Wah I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
43 O

sets O
HK$ B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
HONG B-LOC
KONG I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ka B-ORG
Wah I-ORG
Bank I-ORG
43 O

's O
HK$ B-MISC
Markets I-ORG

arranger O
HSBC B-ORG
Markets I-ORG

six-month O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Interbank I-ORG

-- O
Hong B-ORG
Kong I-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombia B-LOC
reach O

, O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MIAMI B-LOC

The O
U.S. B-LOC
governments O

and O
Colombian B-MISC
Corp I-ORG

allow O
AMR B-ORG
Corp I-ORG
Airlines I-ORG

's O
American B-ORG
Airlines I-ORG
York I-LOC

between O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
, O

and O
Bogota B-LOC
of I-ORG

the O
Department B-ORG
of I-ORG
Transportation I-ORG

in O
Miami B-LOC
also O

, O
AMR B-ORG
and O

between O
Miami B-LOC
to O

and O
Colombia B-LOC
York I-LOC

its O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

The O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombia B-LOC
York I-LOC

the O
Federal B-ORG
Aviation I-ORG
Administration I-ORG
Aviation I-MISC

's O
International B-MISC
Aviation I-MISC
Safety I-MISC
program I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombia B-LOC

when O
Colombia B-LOC
's O

down O
American B-ORG
York I-LOC

between O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
, O

and O
Bogota B-LOC
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
were O

the O
Colombians B-MISC
airlines O

two O
Colombian B-MISC
and O

, O
Avianca B-ORG
. O

and O
ACES B-ORG

- O
DALGLISH B-PER
PARTING O

OVER O
BLACKBURN B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Kenny B-PER
Dalglish I-PER
, O

leaving O
Blackburn B-ORG
premier O

the O
English B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Blackburn B-ORG
had O

and O
Dalglish B-PER

taking O
Blackburn B-ORG

in O
Spain B-LOC
said O

, O
Dalglish B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Dalglish B-PER
for O

with O
Blackburn B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Deutsche B-ORG
Bahn I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
FRANKFURT B-LOC

state-owned O
German B-MISC
Bahn I-ORG

-- O
Frankfurt B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

of O
Algeria B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
PARIS B-LOC

An O
Algerian B-MISC
on O

of O
Algiers B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Algerian B-MISC
Haroun I-LOC

of O
Bou B-LOC
Haroun I-LOC
. O

of O
Algiers B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
El-Watan B-ORG

in O
Algeria B-LOC

, O
Human B-ORG
Rights I-ORG
National I-ORG
Observatory I-ORG
rebels O

on O
Moslem B-MISC

50,000 O
Algerians B-MISC
rebels O

pitting O
Moslem B-MISC
had O

radical O
Islamists B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Malaysia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
KUALA B-LOC
LUMPUR I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Malaysia B-LOC

Minister O
Chua B-PER
Jui I-PER
news O

national O
Bernama B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Chua B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
RTRS B-ORG
savings O

boost O
Australia B-LOC
. O

- O
RBA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CANBERRA B-LOC

The O
Australian B-MISC
Bank I-ORG

the O
Reserve B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
Australia I-ORG
) O

( O
RBA B-ORG

the O
RBA B-ORG

the O
Australian B-MISC
government O

Australian B-MISC
Coalition B-ORG
5.65 O

of O
A$ B-MISC

was O
A$ B-MISC

-- O
Sydney B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

the O
RBA B-ORG

- O
PAKISTAN B-LOC
- O

V O
ENGLAND B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Saeed B-PER
Anwar I-PER
b O

c O
Croft B-PER
176 O

b O
Cork B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Aamir B-PER
Sohail I-PER
b O

c O
Cork B-PER
46 O

b O
Croft B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ijaz B-PER
Ahmed I-PER
b O

c O
Stewart B-PER
61 O

b O
Mullally B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Inzamam-ul-Haq B-PER
b O

c O
Hussain B-PER
35 O

b O
Mullally B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Salim B-PER
Malik I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Asif B-PER
Mujtaba I-PER

- O
Wasim B-PER
Akram I-PER
Khan I-PER

, O
Moin B-PER
Khan I-PER
Ahmed I-PER

, O
Mushtaq B-PER
Ahmed I-PER
Younis I-PER

, O
Waqar B-PER
Younis I-PER
Akam I-PER

, O
Mohammad B-PER
Akam I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
French B-MISC
. O

- O
Juppe B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
BREGANCON B-LOC
1996-08-25 O

, O
France B-LOC

Minister O
Alain B-PER
Juppe I-PER

President O
Jacques B-PER
Chirac I-PER
fortress O

a O
Riviera B-LOC

-- O
Paris B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
India B-LOC
chief O

India B-LOC
RBI B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
DELHI I-LOC

The O
Reserve B-ORG
bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
India I-ORG
Rangarajan I-PER

governor O
C. B-PER
Rangarajan I-PER

told O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rangarajan B-PER

-- O
New B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC

- O
GLORIA B-ORG
BISTRITA I-ORG
VALLETTA I-ORG

2-1 O
F.C. B-ORG
VALLETTA I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BISTRITA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG
) O

( O
Romania B-LOC
Valletta I-ORG

) O
F.C. B-ORG
Valletta I-ORG
) O

( O
Malta B-LOC
winners I-MISC

their O
Cup B-MISC
winners I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG
Lazar I-PER

- O
Ilie B-PER
Lazar I-PER
Voica I-PER

, O
Eugen B-PER
Voica I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
F.C. B-ORG
La I-ORG
Valletta I-ORG
Agius I-PER

- O
Gilbert B-PER
Agius I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG
winners I-MISC

the O
Cup B-MISC
winners I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
REUTER B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ulster B-ORG
Petroleums I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CALGARY B-LOC

Shr O
C$ B-MISC
0.08 O

0.04 O
C$ B-MISC

Shr O
C$ B-MISC
0.15 O

0.12 O
C$ B-MISC

-- O
Reuters B-ORG
Toronto I-ORG
Bureau I-ORG

- O
Kennedy B-PER
both O

and O
Phelan B-PER
squad O

of O
Irish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
DUBLIN B-LOC

the O
Republic B-LOC
of I-LOC
Ireland I-LOC
Cup I-MISC

1998 O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
on O

against O
Liechenstein B-LOC
Association I-ORG

the O
Football B-ORG
Association I-ORG
of I-ORG
Ireland I-ORG

The O
F.A.I. B-ORG
striker O

that O
Liverpool B-ORG
Kennedy I-PER

striker O
Mark B-PER
Kennedy I-PER
defender O

and O
Chelsea B-ORG
Phelan I-PER

defender O
Terry B-PER
Phelan I-PER
for O

to O
Liechenstein B-LOC

-- O
Damien B-PER
Lynch I-PER
Newsroom I-ORG

, O
Dublin B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BNZ B-ORG
fixed O

cuts O
NZ B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
WELLINGTON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Bank B-ORG
of I-ORG
New I-ORG
Zealand I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BNZ B-ORG

-- O
Wellington B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
UN B-ORG
deal O

says O
Iraqi B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
UNITED B-ORG
NATIONS I-ORG

senior O
U.N. B-ORG
oil-for-food O

the O
Iraqi B-MISC

- O
SCOTTISH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
GLASGOW B-LOC

of O
Scottish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Hibernian B-ORG
0 O

0 O
Dunfermline B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Kilmarnock B-ORG
3 O

1 O
Celtic B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Raith B-ORG
3 O

0 O
Motherwell B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rangers B-ORG
United I-ORG

1 O
Dundee B-ORG
United I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Aberdeen B-ORG
END_TAG O

v O
Hearts B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Airdrieonians B-ORG
Fife I-ORG

0 O
East B-ORG
Fife I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Dundee B-ORG
Morton I-ORG

2 O
Greenock B-ORG
Morton I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Falkirk B-ORG
0 O

1 O
Partick B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
St B-ORG
Mirren I-ORG
Johnstone I-ORG

0 O
St B-ORG
Johnstone I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Berwick B-ORG
6 O

0 O
Stenhousemuir B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Brechin B-ORG
1 O

1 O
Ayr B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hamilton B-ORG
0 O

2 O
Clyde B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Queen B-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
South I-ORG
1 O

2 O
Dumbarton B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Stranraer B-ORG
2 O

1 O
Livingston B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Alloa B-ORG
1 O

1 O
Arbroath B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Cowdenbeath B-ORG
0 O

1 O
Monstrose B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Forfar B-ORG
1 O

3 O
Inverness B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Ross B-ORG
County I-ORG
's I-ORG

1 O
Queen B-ORG
's I-ORG
Park I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
East B-ORG
Stirling I-ORG
1 O

0 O
Albion B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Finnish B-MISC
. O

- O
NCB B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
HELSINKI B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Finland B-LOC
Customs I-ORG

the O
National B-ORG
Customs I-ORG
Board I-ORG
) O

( O
NCB B-ORG

, O
NCB B-ORG

The O
Bank B-ORG
of I-ORG
Finland I-ORG

The O
NCB B-ORG
joined O

when O
Finland B-LOC
Union I-ORG

the O
European B-ORG
Union I-ORG

-- O
Helsinki B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

Oldest O
Albania B-LOC
- O

from O
Vatican B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
TIRANA B-LOC

written O
Albanian B-MISC
archives O

the O
Vatican B-LOC
newspaper O

an O
Albanian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gazeta B-ORG
Shqiptare I-ORG
of I-MISC

the O
Book B-MISC
of I-MISC
Mass I-MISC
Buzuku I-PER

by O
Gjon B-PER
Buzuku I-PER
, O

in O
Rome B-LOC
language O

the O
Albanian B-MISC

We O
Albanians B-MISC
, O

of O
Buzuku B-MISC
Hamiti I-PER

scholar O
Musa B-PER
Hamiti I-PER
library O

the O
Vatican B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Tirana B-LOC
of I-MISC

the O
Book B-MISC
of I-MISC
Mass I-MISC

, O
Gazeta B-ORG
Shqiptare I-ORG

southern O
Croatia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
ZAGREB B-LOC

a O
Serb B-MISC
on O

southern O
Croatia B-LOC
reported O

agency O
Hina B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
HINA B-ORG
Gornji I-LOC

of O
Karin B-LOC
Gornji I-LOC
, O

of O
Zadar B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Zadar B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
HINA B-ORG
hinterland O

the O
Zadar B-LOC
lived O

of O
Serbs B-MISC
's O

over O
Croatia B-LOC
federation O

the O
Yugoslav B-MISC

of O
Krajina B-LOC
in O

minority O
Serbs B-MISC
army O

the O
Croatian B-MISC

- O
MAJOR B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

of O
Major B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
American B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
California B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

7 O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
DETROIT B-ORG
4 O

7 O
Chicago B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Milwaukee B-ORG
7 O

10 O
MINNESOTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BOSTON B-ORG
4 O

6 O
Oakland B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BALTIMORE B-ORG
5 O

10 O
Seattle B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Texas B-ORG
8 O

10 O
CLEVELAND B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Toronto B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

6 O
KANSAS B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
National B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-ORG
3 O

8 O
Florida B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SAN B-ORG
FRANCISCO I-ORG
York I-ORG

12 O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
ATLANTA B-ORG
3 O

4 O
Cincinnati B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Pittsburgh B-ORG
2 O

5 O
HOUSTON B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
COLORADO B-ORG
Louis I-ORG

10 O
St B-ORG
Louis I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Philadelphia B-ORG
ANGELES I-ORG

6 O
LOS B-ORG
ANGELES I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SAN B-ORG
DIEGO I-ORG
2 O

7 O
Montreal B-ORG

Rugby O
league-Australian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SYDNEY B-LOC

of O
Australian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Sydney B-ORG
Bulldogs I-ORG
Queensland I-ORG

17 O
South B-ORG
Queensland I-ORG
38 O

16 O
Brisbane B-ORG
Coast I-ORG

38 O
Gold B-ORG
Coast I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
North B-ORG
Sydney I-ORG
Sydney I-ORG

46 O
South B-ORG
Sydney I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Illawarra B-ORG
2 O

42 O
Penrith B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
St B-ORG
George I-ORG
Queensland I-ORG

20 O
North B-ORG
Queensland I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Manly B-ORG
Suburbs I-ORG

42 O
Western B-ORG
Suburbs I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Parramatta B-ORG
Tigers I-ORG

14 O
Sydney B-ORG
Tigers I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Newcastle B-ORG
Reds I-ORG

24 O
Western B-ORG
Reds I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Canberra B-ORG
6 O

30 O
Auckland B-ORG

-- O
Sydney B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
's O

approves O
Arafat B-PER
Bank I-LOC

to O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
JERUSALEM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
President O

gave O
Palestinian B-MISC
Arafat I-PER

President O
Yasser B-PER
Arafat I-PER
Bank I-LOC

the O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC
crisis O

brief O
Israeli-PLO B-MISC
adviser O

an O
Arafat B-PER

through O
Israeli B-MISC
Bank I-LOC

the O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC
Abu I-PER

, O
Nabil B-PER
Abu I-PER
Rdainah I-PER
. O

told O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Arafat B-PER
prime O

former O
Israeli B-MISC
Peres I-PER

minister O
Shimon B-PER
Peres I-PER
Bank I-LOC

the O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC
on O

of O
Ramallah B-LOC
after O

to O
Gaza B-LOC
denied O

after O
Israel B-LOC
leader O

the O
Palestinian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Palestinian B-MISC
Netanyahu I-PER

Minister O
Benjamin B-PER
Netanyahu I-PER
meeting O

the O
Ramallah B-LOC
grounded O

keeping O
Arafat B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Arafat B-PER
and O

between O
Israeli B-MISC
officials O

and O
PLO B-ORG
Bridge I-LOC

the O
Allenby B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
and O

between O
Jordan B-LOC
Bank I-LOC

the O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Abu B-PER
Rdainah I-PER
had O

said O
Arafat B-PER
Bank I-LOC

the O
West B-LOC
Bank I-LOC
lifted O

after O
Israel B-LOC
and O

in O
Gaza B-LOC

Fifty O
Russians B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
MOSCOW B-LOC

50 O
Russian B-MISC
capital O

the O
Chechen B-MISC
on O

capital O
Grozny B-LOC
and O

after O
Russia B-LOC
news O

, O
Interfax B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Interfax B-ORG
military O

quoted O
Russian B-MISC
as O

in O
Chechnya B-LOC
ministry I-ORG

200 O
interior B-ORG
ministry I-ORG
Square I-LOC

at O
Minutka B-LOC
Square I-LOC

The O
Interfax B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Moscow B-LOC
Lebed I-PER

peacemaker O
Alexander B-PER
Lebed I-PER
Maskhadov I-PER

chief-of-staff O
Aslan B-PER
Maskhadov I-PER
) O

0800 O
GMT B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Interfax B-ORG
ministry I-ORG

the O
interior B-ORG
ministry I-ORG
. O

1500 O
GMT B-MISC

1600 O
GMT B-MISC
said O

, O
Interfax B-ORG

the O
Russian B-MISC
as O

in O
Chechnya B-LOC

- O
GERMAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BONN B-LOC

of O
Bundesliga B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Hansa B-ORG
Rostock I-ORG
1 O

0 O
Hamburg B-ORG
64th O

( O
Baeron B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
St B-ORG
Pauli I-ORG
15th O

( O
Driller B-PER
54th O

, O
Trulsen B-PER
64th O

, O
Springer B-PER
67th O

, O
Sobotzik B-PER
4 O

) O
Schalke B-ORG
11th O

( O
Max B-PER
34th O

, O
Thon B-PER
38th O

, O
Wilmots B-PER
64th O

, O
Springer B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
India B-LOC
polls O

disrupt O
Kashmir B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SRINAGAR B-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
India B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
India B-LOC
on O

accused O
Pakistan B-LOC
and O

troubled O
Jammu B-LOC
state O

and O
Kashmir B-LOC

, O
Inderjit B-PER
Gupta I-PER
. O

capital O
Srinagar B-LOC

from O
New B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
India B-LOC
of O

accused O
Pakistan B-LOC
has O

charge O
Islamabad B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gupta B-PER
valley O

the O
Kashmir B-LOC

, O
Gupta B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
India B-LOC
have O

and O
Pakistan B-LOC
since O

of O
Kashmir B-LOC
in O

from O
Britain B-LOC

Minister O
H.D. B-PER
Deve I-PER
Gowda I-PER
and O

in O
Jammu B-LOC
, O

and O
Kashmir B-LOC

fighting O
New B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
RTRS B-ORG
shares O

- O
Niugini B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SYDNEY B-LOC

miner O
Niugini B-ORG
Mining I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
3.75 O

to O
A$ B-MISC
Mountain I-ORG

from O
Battle B-ORG
Mountain I-ORG
Gold I-ORG
it O

of O
Niugini B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Niugini B-ORG
Mining I-ORG
Ltd I-ORG
Mountain I-ORG

that O
Battle B-ORG
Mountain I-ORG
it O

in O
Niugini B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Battle B-ORG
Mountain I-ORG
broker O

a O
Sydney B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Niugini B-ORG
, O

in O
Australia B-LOC
and O

, O
Chile B-LOC
New I-LOC

and O
Papua B-LOC
New I-LOC
Guinea I-LOC
gold O

the O
Lihir B-ORG

0025 O
GMT B-MISC
Mining I-ORG

, O
Niugini B-ORG
Mining I-ORG
3.65 O

at O
A$ B-MISC

-- O
Sydney B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

OF O
S. B-MISC
KOREAN I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SEOUL B-LOC

of O
South B-MISC
Korean I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Samsung B-ORG
3 O

13 O
Hyundai B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Haitai B-ORG
4 O

5 O
Hanwha B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
OB B-ORG
2 O

4 O
Lotte B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Ssangbangwool B-ORG
0 O

1 O
LG B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Haitai B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Ssangbangwool B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hanwha B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hyundai B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Samsung B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lotte B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LG B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
OB B-ORG

- O
FRENCH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
PARIS B-LOC

a O
French B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nancy B-ORG
St I-ORG

0 O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
Germain I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Oppenheimer B-ORG
Capital I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Oppenheimer B-ORG
Capital I-ORG
LP I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SOLIDERE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BEIRUT B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SOLIDERE B-ORG
Secondary I-ORG

( O
BSM B-ORG

the O
Beirut B-LOC
is O

district O
SOLIDERE B-ORG

on O
BSM B-ORG
shares O

only O
SOLIDERE B-ORG

official O
Beirut B-ORG
Stock I-ORG
Exchange I-ORG
Libanais I-ORG

1,185 O
Ciments B-ORG
Libanais I-ORG

: O
Ciments B-ORG
Blancs I-ORG
and O

and O
Uniceramic B-ORG

The O
BLOM B-MISC
Stock I-MISC
Index I-MISC
index O

the O
LISPI B-MISC

- O
Beirut B-LOC

- O
POLLOCK B-PER
CAREER O

CONCLUDES O
WARWICKSHIRE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
Pollock I-PER

bowler O
Shaun B-PER
Pollock I-PER
career O

his O
Warwickshire B-ORG
. O

over O
Worcestershire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Pollock B-PER
were O

as O
Worcestershire B-ORG

, O
Warwickshire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Warwickshire B-ORG
, O

behind O
Yorkshire B-ORG
and O

, O
Nottinghamshire B-ORG
. O

and O
Surrey B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Yorkshire B-ORG
Byas I-PER

captain O
David B-PER
Byas I-PER
. O

against O
Lancashire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lancashire B-ORG
put O

before O
Byas B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Yorkshire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Gateway B-ORG
Data I-ORG
Sciences I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PHOENIX B-LOC

of O
Consolidated B-ORG
Financial I-ORG
Data I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
GREEK B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ATHENS B-LOC

The O
Greek B-MISC
Simitis I-PER

Minister O
Costas B-PER
Simitis I-PER
Skandalidis I-PER

secretary O
Costas B-PER
Skandalidis I-PER

Minister O
Costas B-PER
Simitis I-PER
. O

said O
Skandalidis B-PER

-- O
Dimitris B-PER
Kontogiannis I-PER
Newsroom I-ORG

, O
Athens B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
NOVYE B-LOC
ATAGI I-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
Russia B-LOC

the O
Chechen B-MISC
have O

capital O
Grozny B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Senegal B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
DAKAR B-LOC

central O
Senegal B-LOC
, O

of O
Kaolack B-LOC

Doctor O
Masserigne B-PER
Ndiaye I-PER

told O
Reuters B-ORG
capital O

the O
Senegalese B-MISC
. O

capital O
Dakar B-LOC

- O
Iraq B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BAGHDAD B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
JUMHOURIYA B-ORG

- O
Istanbul B-LOC
to O

urges O
Ankara B-LOC
. O

with O
Iraq B-LOC

from O
Arab B-MISC
with O

supply O
Iraq B-LOC

blames O
U.S. B-LOC
rebels O

between O
Kurdish B-MISC
. O

northern O
Iraq B-LOC

in O
Iraq B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
QADISSIYA B-ORG

- O
Iraq B-LOC
warplanes O

by O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
IRAQ B-LOC

lambasts O
Jalal B-PER
Talabani I-PER
rebel O

a O
Kurdish B-MISC
in O

with O
Iran B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BABEL B-ORG

Blaming O
Iraq B-LOC
is O

in O
Jordan B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MONTGOMERY B-LOC
. O

, O
Ala B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
KinderCare B-ORG
Learning I-ORG
Centers I-ORG
Inc I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Philip B-PER
Maslowe I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

, O
British B-MISC

at O
Oxford B-ORG
University I-ORG

the O
Oxford B-LOC

the O
British B-ORG
Heart I-ORG
Foundation I-ORG
Pharma I-ORG

and O
Lichtwer B-ORG
Pharma I-ORG
GmbH I-ORG
brand O

makes O
Kwai B-MISC

-- O
London B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Greek B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ATHENS B-LOC

The O
Greek B-MISC
Simitis I-PER

Minister O
Costas B-PER
Simitis I-PER
Skandalidis I-PER

secretary O
Costas B-PER
Skandalidis I-PER

Minister O
Costas B-PER
Simitis I-PER
. O

said O
Skandalidis B-PER

-- O
Dimitris B-PER
Kontogiannis I-PER
Newsroom I-ORG

, O
Athens B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
Korean I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SEOUL B-LOC

at O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
University I-ORG

's O
Yonsei B-ORG
University I-ORG

with O
North B-LOC
Korea I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Buffett B-PER
Capital I-ORG

raises O
Property B-ORG
Capital I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
WASHINGTON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Omaha B-LOC
Buffett I-PER

billionaire O
Warren B-PER
Buffett I-PER
Capital I-ORG

in O
Property B-ORG
Capital I-ORG
Trust I-ORG

, O
Buffett B-PER
real O

the O
Boston-based B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Buffett B-PER
Hathaway I-ORG

of O
Berkshire B-ORG
Hathaway I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
companies O

large O
U.S. B-LOC

AT O
TOSHIBA B-MISC
CLASSIC I-MISC

05:30 O
GMT B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
CARLSBAD B-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
California B-LOC

450,000 O
Toshiba B-MISC
Classic I-MISC

- O
Conchita B-PER
Martinez I-PER
) O

( O
Spain B-LOC
Tauziat I-PER

( O
France B-LOC

- O
Gabriela B-PER
Sabatini I-PER
) O

( O
Argentina B-LOC
Carlsson I-PER

beat O
Asa B-PER
Carlsson I-PER
) O

( O
Sweden B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Katarina B-PER
Studenikova I-PER
) O

( O
Slovakia B-LOC
Habsudova I-PER

- O
Karina B-PER
Habsudova I-PER

( O
Slovakia B-LOC

that O
Habsudova B-PER

OF O
GERMAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BONN B-LOC

of O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Bochum B-ORG
66th O

( O
Jack B-PER
Bielefeld I-ORG

) O
Arminia B-ORG
Bielefeld I-ORG
59th O

( O
Molata B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Borussia B-ORG
Moenchengladbach I-ORG
22nd O

( O
Andersson B-PER
3 O

) O
Karlsruhe B-ORG

( O
Haessler B-PER
45th O

, O
Dundee B-PER
90th O

, O
Keller B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Stuttgart B-ORG
50th O

( O
Balakow B-PER
61st O

, O
Bobic B-PER
Bremen I-ORG

) O
Werder B-ORG
Bremen I-ORG
END_TAG O

( O
Votava B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
1860 B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
38th O

( O
Schwabl B-PER
Dortmund I-ORG

) O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
END_TAG O

( O
Zorc B-PER

, O
Moeller B-PER
90th O

, O
Heinrich B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Bayer B-ORG
Leverkusen I-ORG
Duesseldorf I-ORG

0 O
Fortuna B-ORG
Duesseldorf I-ORG
47th O

( O
Seeliger B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Freiburg B-ORG
52nd O

( O
Zeyer B-PER
3 O

) O
Cologne B-ORG
9th O

( O
Gaissmayer B-PER
END_TAG O

, O
Polster B-PER

- O
France B-LOC
Monde I-ORG

- O
Le B-ORG
Monde I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PARIS B-LOC

daily O
Le B-ORG
Monde I-ORG

-- O
Africans B-MISC
Juppe I-PER

Minister O
Alain B-PER
Juppe I-PER
church O

in O
Paris B-LOC

-- O
FLNC B-ORG
nationalist O

FLNC B-ORG
Corsican B-MISC

of O
Bally B-ORG
factories O

's O
French B-MISC
manufacturers O

with O
French B-MISC

the O
Sud-PTT B-MISC
Telecom I-ORG

at O
France B-ORG
Telecom I-ORG

-- O
Paris B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

- O
PAKISTAN B-LOC
-- O

V O
ENGLAND B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Pakistan B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC
's O

to O
England B-LOC

: O
England B-LOC
Crawley I-PER

( O
J. B-PER
Crawley I-PER
Thorpe I-PER

, O
G. B-PER
Thorpe I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Waqar B-PER
Younis I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Pakistan B-LOC
Anwar I-PER

( O
Saeed B-PER
Anwar I-PER
Ahmed I-PER

, O
Ijaz B-PER
Ahmed I-PER

- O
ENGLAND B-LOC
IN O

V O
PAKISTAN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC
at O

against O
Pakistan B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

: O
England B-LOC
Crawley I-PER

( O
J. B-PER
Crawley I-PER
Thorpe I-PER

, O
G. B-PER
Thorpe I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Waqar B-PER
Younis I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
FRANKFURT B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
German B-MISC
office I-ORG

the O
Federal B-ORG
office I-ORG
for I-ORG
motor I-ORG
vehicles I-ORG

of O
Germans B-MISC
cars O

buying O
German B-MISC

all O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Volkswagen B-ORG
AG I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Opel B-ORG
AG I-ORG
Motors I-ORG

with O
General B-ORG
Motors I-ORG

was O
Ford B-ORG

Only O
Seat B-ORG
had O

and O
Porsche B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Seat B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Porsche B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Yeltsin B-PER
television O

on O
Russian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
MOSCOW B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Russian B-MISC
Yeltsin I-PER

of O
Boris B-PER
Yeltsin I-PER
Dmitrieva I-PER

minister O
Tatyana B-PER
Dmitrieva I-PER

the O
Kremlin B-LOC
. O

northwestern O
Russia B-LOC

AT O
HAMLET B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COMMACK B-LOC
York I-LOC

, O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Cup B-MISC

- O
Andrei B-PER
Medvedev I-PER
) O

( O
Ukraine B-LOC
Damm I-PER

beat O
Martin B-PER
Damm I-PER
END_TAG O

( O
Czech B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Luke B-PER
Jensen I-PER
Jensen I-PER

and O
Murphy B-PER
Jensen I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
Volkov I-PER

beat O
Alexander B-PER
Volkov I-PER

( O
Russia B-LOC
Dreekmann I-PER

and O
Handrik B-PER
Dreekmann I-PER
) O

( O
Germany B-LOC

ON O
RAVANELLI B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Middlesbrough B-ORG
striker O

's O
Italian B-MISC
Ravanelli I-PER

striker O
Fabrizio B-PER
Ravanelli I-PER

and O
Middlesbrough B-ORG

seen O
Ravanelli B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ravanelli B-PER
on O

at O
Chelsea B-ORG
Forest I-LOC

at O
Nottingham B-LOC
Forest I-LOC
Robson I-PER

manager O
Bryan B-PER
Robson I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Netanyahu B-PER
consult O

, O
Weizman B-PER
invitation O

on O
Arafat B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
JERUSALEM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israeli B-MISC
Weizman I-PER

President O
Ezer B-PER
Weizman I-PER
Arafat I-PER

with O
Yasser B-PER
Arafat I-PER
Netanyahu I-PER

Minister O
Benjamin B-PER
Netanyahu I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Weizman B-PER
met O

and O
Netanyahu B-PER
residence O

official O
Jerusalem B-LOC

in O
Israel B-LOC
Ahronoth I-ORG

's O
Yedioth B-ORG
Ahronoth I-ORG
had O

that O
Weizman B-PER
to O

invited O
Arafat B-PER
peace O

the O
Israel-PLO B-MISC

, O
Aryeh B-PER
Shumer I-PER
and O

that O
Weizman B-PER
should O

and O
Arafat B-PER
leader O

the O
Palestinian B-MISC
president O

the O
Israeli B-MISC
Ahronoth I-ORG

which O
Yedioth B-ORG
Ahronoth I-ORG

said O
Netanyahu B-PER
himself O

meeting O
Arafat B-PER
and O

between O
Weizman B-PER
president O

the O
Palestinian B-MISC

After O
Moslem B-MISC
in O

in O
Israel B-LOC
called O

, O
Weizman B-PER
to O

the O
PLO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Shumer B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Albanian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
TIRANA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Albania B-LOC
Party I-ORG

opposition O
Socialist B-ORG
Party I-ORG
dictatorship O

of O
Stalinist B-MISC
country O

the O
Balkan B-LOC

Socialist O
Zeri B-ORG
i I-ORG
Popullit I-ORG

leader O
Fatos B-PER
Nano I-PER
of O

conservative O
Democrats B-MISC
Berisha I-PER

President O
Sali B-PER
Berisha I-PER

leader O
Servet B-PER
Pellumbi I-PER
Marx I-PER

of O
Karl B-PER
Marx I-PER

Secretary-General O
Gramoz B-PER
Ruci I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
man O

executes O
Pakistani B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
DUBAI B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC
man O

a O
Pakistani B-MISC
television O

, O
Saudi B-MISC

an O
Interior B-ORG
Ministry I-ORG
Ahmad I-PER

saying O
Shabir B-PER
Ahmad I-PER
Muhammad I-PER
Jalil I-PER
. O

in O
Mecca B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Saudi B-LOC
Arabia I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nigerian B-MISC
ECOMOG B-ORG

over O
Liberia B-LOC
force O

Liberia B-LOC
ECOMOG B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
MONROVIA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nigerian B-MISC
Victor I-PER

General O
Sam B-PER
Victor I-PER
Malu I-PER
peacekeeping O

the O
ECOMOG B-ORG
, O

in O
Liberia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Malu B-PER
major O

another O
Nigerian B-MISC
Inienger I-PER

, O
John B-PER
Inienger I-PER
after O

for O
Liberia B-LOC

in O
Liberia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
United B-ORG
Nations I-ORG
on O

of O
Tubmanburg B-LOC
special O

, O
U.N. B-ORG
Nyakyi I-PER

representative O
Anthony B-PER
Nyakyi I-PER

the O
ULIMO-J B-ORG

the O
Nigerian B-MISC
on O

capital O
Abuja B-LOC

The O
ECOMOG B-ORG
by O

- O
SALAH B-PER
HISSOU I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
BRUSSELS B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Morocco B-LOC
Hissou I-PER

's O
Salah B-PER
Hissou I-PER
grand O

the O
Brussels B-LOC

by O
Ethiopia B-LOC
Gebreselassie I-PER

's O
Haile B-PER
Gebreselassie I-PER
town O

the O
Dutch B-MISC
in O

of O
Hengelo B-LOC

AT O
HAMLET B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COMMACK B-LOC
York I-LOC

, O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Waldbaum B-MISC
Hamlet I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Adrian B-PER
Voinea I-PER
) O

( O
Romania B-LOC
Johansson I-PER

( O
Sweden B-LOC

- O
Andrei B-PER
Medvedev I-PER
) O

( O
Ukraine B-LOC
Stark I-PER

beat O
Jonathan B-PER
Stark I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Martin B-PER
Damm I-PER
Republic I-LOC

( O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
Joyce I-PER

beat O
Michael B-PER
Joyce I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Karol B-PER
Kucera I-PER
) O

( O
Slovakia B-LOC
Chang I-PER

- O
Michael B-PER
Chang I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Malawi B-LOC
says O

ex-president O
Banda B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
BLANTYRE B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Malawi B-LOC
Banda I-PER

, O
Kamuzu B-PER
Banda I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Banda B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Malawi B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
AMMAN B-LOC

after O
Amman B-LOC
and O

blamed O
Iraq B-LOC
local O

a O
pro-Baghdad B-MISC

said O
Ibrahim B-PER
. O

in O
Amman B-LOC

shook O
Jordan B-LOC
and O

of O
Karak B-LOC
. O

to O
Amman B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Turkey B-LOC
rebels O

17 O
Kurd B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
ANKARA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Turkish B-MISC
rebels O

17 O
Kurdish B-MISC
news O

state-run O
Anatolian B-ORG

with O
Kurdistan B-ORG
Workers I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O

( O
PKK B-ORG

in O
Van B-LOC
and O

in O
Sirnak B-LOC
. O

in O
Hakkari B-LOC

the O
PKK B-ORG
. O

southeastern O
Turkey B-LOC

by O
PKK B-ORG
reported O

, O
Anatolian B-ORG

mostly O
Kurdish B-MISC
, O

the O
PKK B-ORG
. O

of O
Diyarbakir B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
RUGBY B-ORG
UNION I-ORG
ZEALAND I-LOC

- O
NEW B-LOC
ZEALAND I-LOC
AFRICA I-LOC

IN O
SOUTH B-LOC
AFRICA I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
PRETORIA B-LOC
Africa I-LOC

, O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
Africa I-LOC

in O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC

the O
All B-ORG
Blacks I-ORG

the O
Springboks B-ORG
Blacks I-ORG

the O
All B-ORG
Blacks I-ORG

wing O
Jeff B-PER
Wilson I-PER
Zealand I-LOC

gave O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
Kruger I-PER

flanker O
Ruben B-PER
Kruger I-PER
van I-PER

scrum-half O
Joost B-PER
van I-PER
der I-PER
Westhuizen I-PER

The O
Springboks B-ORG
Stransky I-PER

fly-half O
Joel B-PER
Stransky I-PER
Zealand I-LOC

and O
New B-LOC
Zealand I-LOC
Preston I-PER

fly-half O
Jon B-PER
Preston I-PER
Brooke I-PER

eight O
Zinzan B-PER
Brooke I-PER

- O
MILLNS B-PER
. O

FOR O
BOLAND B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CAPE B-LOC
TOWN I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
said O

side O
Boland B-ORG
fast O

signed O
Leicestershire B-ORG
Millns I-PER

bowler O
David B-PER
Millns I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Millns B-MISC
with O

toured O
Australia B-LOC
A O

with O
England B-LOC
all-rounder O

former O
England B-LOC
DeFreitas I-PER

all-rounder O
Phillip B-PER
DeFreitas I-PER
's O

as O
Boland B-ORG

- O
Lehman B-ORG
. O

starts O
SNET B-ORG

-- O
Lehman B-ORG
Bath I-PER

analyst O
Blake B-PER
Bath I-PER
New I-ORG

-- O
Southern B-ORG
New I-ORG
England I-ORG

-- O
E. B-PER
Auchard I-PER
Street I-ORG

, O
Wall B-ORG
Street I-ORG
bureau I-ORG

- O
CBI B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

in O
UK B-LOC
of I-ORG

( O
CBI B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CBI B-ORG

the O
UK B-LOC

-- O
Rosemary B-PER
Bennett I-PER
Newsroom I-ORG

, O
London B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

- O
MICKELSON B-PER
. O

IN O
AKRON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
AKRON B-LOC
1996-08-25 O

, O
Ohio B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Phil B-PER
Mickelson I-PER
Series I-MISC

win O
World B-MISC
Series I-MISC
of I-MISC
Golf I-MISC
Mayfair I-PER

over O
Billy B-PER
Mayfair I-PER

for O
Mickelson B-PER
Mayfair I-PER

with O
Billy B-PER
Mayfair I-PER

with O
Mayfiar B-PER
Stricker I-PER

were O
Steve B-PER
Stricker I-PER
Waldorf I-PER

and O
Duffy B-PER
Waldorf I-PER

said O
Mickelson B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Mickelson B-PER
Tour I-MISC

the O
PGA B-MISC
Tour I-MISC

brings O
Mickelson B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Mickelson B-PER
birdied O

when O
Mayfair B-PER
three-putted O

while O
Mickelson B-PER

nine O
Mickelson B-PER
back O

bringing O
Mickelson B-PER
, O

with O
Mayfair B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Mickelson B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Mayfair B-PER

which O
Mayfair B-PER

to O
Greg B-PER
Norman I-PER

behind O
Mickelson B-PER

- O
Ireland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
DUBLIN B-LOC

the O
Irish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
IRISH B-ORG
INDEPENDENT I-ORG

- O
Ireland B-LOC
Permanent I-ORG

lender O
Irish B-ORG
Permanent I-ORG

million O
Irish B-MISC
Taylor I-PER

manager O
Tony B-PER
Taylor I-PER

second O
Japanese B-MISC
Navy I-ORG

the O
Irish B-ORG
Navy I-ORG
Corps I-ORG

and O
Air B-ORG
Corps I-ORG
coast O

the O
Irish B-MISC

into O
Taylor B-ORG
Asset I-ORG
Managers I-ORG

- O
Irish B-MISC
and O

company O
Ivernia B-ORG
African I-MISC

its O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
have O

partner O
Minorco B-ORG
, O

at O
Lisheen B-LOC
Tipperary I-LOC

, O
County B-LOC
Tipperary I-LOC

firm O
CRH B-ORG
stone O

for O
U.S. B-LOC
Inc I-ORG

business O
Tilcon B-ORG
Inc I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
IRISH B-ORG
TIMES I-ORG

a O
County B-LOC
Antrim I-LOC
Ireland I-LOC

in O
Northern B-LOC
Ireland I-LOC

in O
Irish B-MISC
Stores I-ORG

chain O
Dunnes B-ORG
Stores I-ORG

the O
London B-LOC
bankers O

of O
U.S. B-LOC
Lynch I-ORG

bankers O
Merrill B-ORG
Lynch I-ORG
. O

to O
Dublin B-LOC

The O
Irish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Boskalis B-ORG

13:12 O
GMT B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
PAPENDRECHT B-LOC
1996-08-23 O

, O
Netherlands B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Boskalis B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Kevorkian B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
PONTIAC B-LOC
. O

, O
Mich B-LOC

Dr. O
Jack B-PER
Kevorkian I-PER
woman O

40-year-old O
Missouri B-LOC

Dr O
Robert B-PER
Aranosian I-PER
Osteopathic I-LOC

at O
Pontiac B-LOC
Osteopathic I-LOC
Hospital I-LOC
brought O

said O
Kevorkian B-PER
Smith I-PER

of O
Patricia B-PER
Smith I-PER
Summit I-LOC

of O
Lees B-LOC
Summit I-LOC
. O

, O
Mo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Kevorkian B-PER
Fieger I-PER

, O
Geoffrey B-PER
Fieger I-PER
's O

attending O
Smith B-PER
, O

, O
David B-PER
Poland I-PER

, O
James B-PER
Poland I-PER
. O

and O
Kevorkian B-PER

of O
Kevorkian B-PER

of O
Smith B-PER

, O
Kevorkian B-PER
Siebens I-PER

of O
Louise B-PER
Siebens I-PER
woman O

76-year-old O
Texas B-LOC
Gehrig I-PER

or O
Lou B-PER
Gehrig I-PER

, O
Kevorkian B-PER
Curren I-PER

helped O
Judith B-PER
Curren I-PER
nurse O

42-year-old O
Massachusetts B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nicaraguan B-MISC
for O

to O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MANAGUA B-LOC
1996-08-23 O

, O
Nicaragua B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nicaraguan B-MISC
Chamorro I-PER

President O
Violeta B-PER
Chamorro I-PER
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Chamorro B-PER
in O

to O
Taiwan B-LOC
University I-LOC

to O
Taipei B-LOC
University I-LOC
Hospital I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Chamorro B-PER
for O

to O
Washington B-LOC
Wilson I-PER

, O
Sam B-PER
Wilson I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
China B-LOC
talks O

for O
Taiwan B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BEIJING B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
China B-LOC
and O

with O
Taiwan B-LOC

official O
Xinhua B-ORG
Shubei I-PER

quoted O
Tang B-PER
Shubei I-PER
for I-ORG

- O
ENGLAND B-LOC
521-8 O

; O
PAKISTAN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

: O
England B-LOC
521-8 O

; O
Pakistan B-LOC

- O
KANKKUNEN B-PER
ROLLS O

AS O
MCRAE B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
JYVASKYLA B-LOC
1996-08-24 O

, O
Finland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Finland B-LOC
Kankkunen I-PER

's O
Juha B-PER
Kankkunen I-PER
on O

his O
Toyota B-ORG
Lakes I-MISC

the O
1,000 B-MISC
Lakes I-MISC
Rally I-MISC

champion O
Kankunnen B-PER
Gronholm I-PER

, O
Marcus B-PER
Gronholm I-PER
. O

a O
Toyota B-ORG

leader O
Tommi B-PER
Makinen I-PER
was O

his O
Mitsubishi B-ORG
McRae I-PER

champion O
Colin B-PER
McRae I-PER

the O
British B-MISC
6.5 O

his O
Subaru B-ORG

co-driver O
Derek B-PER
Ringer I-PER
Richards I-PER

boss O
David B-PER
Richards I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Kankkunen B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ford B-ORG
Carlos B-PER

with O
Spaniard B-MISC
Sainz I-PER

Spaniard B-MISC
Carlos B-PER
Sainz I-PER
Bruno B-PER

while O
Belgian B-MISC
Thiry I-PER

Belgian B-MISC
Bruno B-PER
Thiry I-PER

- O
MAJOR B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

of O
Major B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
American B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BOSTON B-ORG
1 O

2 O
Oakland B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Seattle B-ORG
3 O

10 O
BALTIMORE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
California B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

12 O
NEW B-ORG
YORK I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Toronto B-ORG
0 O

1 O
CHICAGO B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Detroit B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

10 O
KANSAS B-ORG
CITY I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Texas B-ORG
2 O

11 O
MINNESOTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
National B-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COLORADO B-ORG
Louis I-ORG

10 O
St B-ORG
Louis I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Cincinnati B-ORG
2 O

3 O
ATLANTA B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Pittsburgh B-ORG
6 O

8 O
HOUSTON B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LOS B-ORG
ANGELES I-ORG
5 O

8 O
Philadelphia B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Montreal B-ORG
FRANCISCO I-ORG

5 O
SAN B-ORG
FRANCISCO I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Argentine B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BUENOS B-LOC
AIRES I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Argentine B-MISC
Industry I-ORG

, O
Steel B-ORG
Industry I-ORG
Center I-ORG

-- O
Jason B-PER
Webb I-PER
Aires I-ORG

, O
Buenos B-ORG
Aires I-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

- O
SCOTTISH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
GLASGOW B-LOC

a O
Scottish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
East B-ORG
Stirling I-ORG
1 O

0 O
Albion B-ORG

pct O
India B-LOC
. O

- O
RBI B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BOMBAY B-LOC

The O
Reserve B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
of I-ORG
India I-ORG
Rangarajan I-PER

Governor O
Chakravarty B-PER
Rangarajan I-PER

, O
Rangarajan B-PER
Delhi I-LOC

in O
New B-LOC
Delhi I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Rangarajan B-PER

-- O
Bombay B-LOC

AT O
HAMLET B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COMMACK B-LOC
York I-LOC

, O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Waldbaum B-MISC
Hamlet I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Martin B-PER
Damm I-PER
Republic I-LOC

( O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
Voinea I-PER

( O
Romania B-LOC

- O
Andrei B-PER
Medvedev I-PER
) O

( O
Ukraine B-LOC
Kucera I-PER

beat O
Karol B-PER
Kucera I-PER
) O

( O
Slovakia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
S. B-MISC
Korean I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
SEOUL B-LOC

- O
PAKISTAN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Pakistan B-LOC

against O
England B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

at O
The B-LOC
Oval I-LOC

: O
England B-LOC
521-8 O

; O
Pakistan B-LOC

- O
Bosnia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SARAJEVO B-LOC

the O
Sarajevo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
OSLOBODJENJE B-ORG

The O
Bosnian B-MISC

the O
Bosnian B-MISC
kuna O

the O
Croatian B-MISC
currency O

new O
Bosnian B-MISC

, O
Mirhunisa B-PER
Komarica I-PER
town O

the O
Bosnian B-MISC
are O

of O
Srebrenica B-LOC
mines O

in O
Serbian B-MISC

to O
Komarica B-PER
work O

of O
Srebrenica B-LOC
mine O

the O
Trepca B-LOC
. O

in O
Aleksandrovac B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
DNEVNI B-ORG
AVAZ I-ORG

- O
Slovenian B-MISC
opposition O

two O
Bosnian B-MISC
and O

in O
Ljubljana B-LOC
and O

in O
Ljubljana B-LOC
. O

and O
Maribor B-LOC

-- O
Sarajevo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nigeria B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LAGOS B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nigerian B-MISC
, O

of O
Sokoto B-LOC

The O
News B-ORG
Agency I-ORG
of I-ORG
Nigeria I-ORG
) O

( O
NAN B-ORG
Shelling I-PER

spokesman O
Umar B-PER
Shelling I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Hassan B-PER
Hafidh I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
BAGHDAD B-LOC

A O
Mujahideen B-ORG
Khalq I-ORG
Rajavi I-PER

leader O
Massoud B-PER
Rajavi I-PER
the O

in O
Baghdad B-LOC
Democratic I-ORG

( O
KDPI B-ORG
Rastegar I-PER

) O
Hassan B-PER
Rastegar I-PER
's O

to O
Iran B-LOC
. O

rebel O
Kurds B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Iran B-LOC
in O

northern O
Iraq B-LOC
guerrillas O

of O
KDPI B-ORG
Kurdish I-MISC

in O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kurdish I-MISC
. O

in O
Baghdad B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kurdish I-MISC
are O

bordering O
Iran B-LOC
Kurdish I-ORG

( O
PUK B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
PUK B-ORG
's O

and O
Iraq B-LOC
Democratic I-ORG

's O
Kurdistan B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O

( O
KDP B-ORG
Kurdish I-MISC

main O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kurdish I-MISC
under O

northern O
Iraq B-LOC
forces O

since O
Iraqi B-MISC
in O

from O
Kuwait B-LOC
War I-MISC

1991 O
Gulf B-MISC
War I-MISC

a O
U.S.-sponsored B-MISC

100 O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kurds I-MISC

Both O
Iran B-LOC
mount O

and O
Turkey B-LOC
in O

northern O
Iraq B-LOC
rebels O

own O
Kurdish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
. O

with O
Syria B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colleen B-PER
Siegel I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
JERUSALEM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
said O

with O
Syria B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Itamar B-PER
Rabinovich I-PER
's O

as O
Israel B-LOC
conducted O

to O
Washington B-LOC
, O

with O
Syria B-LOC
Radio I-ORG

told O
Israel B-ORG
Radio I-ORG
wanted O

like O
Damascus B-LOC

the O
Syrian B-MISC

The O
Syrians B-MISC
is O

in O
Washington B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Rabinovich B-PER

by O
Eliahu B-PER
Ben-Elissar I-PER
envoy O

former O
Israeli B-MISC
and O

to O
Egypt B-LOC
party O

right-wing O
Likud B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
a O

sent O
Syria B-LOC
, O

via O
Washington B-LOC

slammed O
Damascus B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Syria B-LOC
on O

accused O
Israel B-LOC
television O

after O
Israeli B-MISC
had O

that O
Damascus B-LOC

( O
Syrian B-MISC
al- I-PER

President O
Hafez B-PER
al- I-PER
is O

) O
Assad B-PER
is O

that O
Israel B-LOC
Foreign O

, O
Israeli B-MISC
Levy I-PER

Minister O
David B-PER
Levy I-PER
Radio I-ORG

told O
Israel B-ORG
Radio I-ORG

since O
Israeli B-MISC
Netanyahu I-PER

Minister O
Benjamin B-PER
Netanyahu I-PER
Heights I-LOC

the O
Golan B-LOC
Heights I-LOC
in O

from O
Syria B-LOC
East I-LOC

1967 O
Middle B-LOC
East I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Israeli-Syrian B-MISC
since O

the O
Golan B-LOC
concessions O

make O
Golan B-LOC

of O
Damascus B-LOC

, O
Levy B-PER

from O
Syria B-LOC
's O

answer O
Israel B-LOC

, O
God B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Israel B-LOC
Two I-ORG

's O
Channel B-ORG
Two I-ORG
had O

said O
Damascus B-LOC
. O

to O
Israel B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Netanyahu B-PER
's O

and O
Levy B-PER

that O
Netanyahu B-PER
via O

reassure O
Syria B-LOC
, O

via O
Cairo B-LOC
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
. O

and O
Moscow B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
CME B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CHICAGO B-LOC

on O
CME B-ORG

- O
Iraq B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BAGHDAD B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
THAWRA B-ORG

- O
Iraq B-LOC
Hussein I-PER

President O
Saddam B-PER
Hussein I-PER
liberal O

the O
Russian B-MISC
Zhirinovsky I-PER

party O
Vladimir B-PER
Zhirinovsky I-PER

- O
Turkish B-MISC
will O

says O
Turkey B-LOC
trade O

the O
Baghdad B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
IRAQ B-LOC

in O
Umm B-LOC
Qasr I-LOC
. O

the O
Gulf B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BRUSSELS B-LOC

's O
Brussels B-LOC

A O
Belgian B-MISC

OUT-OF-SORTS O
NEWCASTLE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Newcastle B-ORG
Wednesday I-ORG

pacesetters O
Sheffield B-ORG
Wednesday I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC
Shearer I-PER

striker O
Alan B-PER
Shearer I-PER
Keegan I-PER

gave O
Kevin B-PER
Keegan I-PER
Dejan B-PER

's O
Yugoslav B-MISC
Stefanovic I-PER

Yugoslav B-MISC
Dejan B-PER
Stefanovic I-PER
forward O

down O
Colombian B-MISC
Asprilla I-PER

forward O
Faustino B-PER
Asprilla I-PER

later O
Wednesday B-ORG
Atherton I-PER

through O
Peter B-PER
Atherton I-PER
Pembridge I-PER

meet O
Mark B-PER
Pembridge I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Guy B-PER
Whittingham I-PER
side O

the O
Yorkshire B-ORG

to O
Newcastle B-ORG
striker O

, O
England B-LOC
Ferdinand I-PER

striker O
Les B-PER
Ferdinand I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Wednesday B-ORG

hopefuls O
Liverpool B-ORG
, O

newly-promoted O
Sunderland B-ORG
, O

in O
London B-LOC
Hotspur I-ORG

between O
Tottenham B-ORG
Hotspur I-ORG
also O

and O
Everton B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Frenchman B-MISC
LeBoeuf I-PER

Frenchman B-MISC
Frank B-PER
LeBoeuf I-PER
Gianluca B-PER

and O
Italian B-MISC
Vialli I-PER

Italian B-MISC
Gianluca B-PER
Vialli I-PER
beat O

as O
Chelsea B-ORG
2-0 O

beat O
Coventry B-ORG
won O

managerless O
Arsenal B-ORG
. O

at O
Leicester B-LOC

and O
Cup B-MISC
United I-ORG

winners O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
on O

champions O
Blackburn B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Viacom B-ORG
sequel O

plans O
Mission B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LOS B-LOC
ANGELES I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Paramount B-ORG
Pictures I-ORG
Cruise I-PER

the O
Tom B-PER
Cruise I-PER
: I-MISC

, O
Mission B-MISC
: I-MISC
Impossible I-MISC
Variety I-ORG

, O
Daily B-ORG
Variety I-ORG

for O
Viacom B-MISC
Inc-owned I-MISC
since O

Inc-owned I-MISC
Paramount B-ORG
Gump I-MISC

's O
Forrest B-MISC
Gump I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Cruise B-PER
Award-winning I-MISC

meet O
Academy B-MISC
Award-winning I-MISC
Goldman I-PER

screenwriter O
William B-PER
Goldman I-PER

said O
Mission B-MISC
: I-MISC
Impossible I-MISC
De I-PER

director O
Brian B-PER
De I-PER
Palma I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Goldman B-PER
were O

whose O
Oscars B-MISC
Cassidy I-MISC

for O
Butch B-MISC
Cassidy I-MISC
and I-MISC
the I-MISC
Sundance I-MISC
Kid I-MISC
the I-MISC

and O
All B-MISC
the I-MISC
President I-MISC
's I-MISC
Men I-MISC

out O
Mission B-MISC
: I-MISC
Impossible I-MISC
Variety I-ORG

, O
Daily B-ORG
Variety I-ORG

FOR O
AUSTRALIANS B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COLOMBO B-LOC

when O
Australia B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

of O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Australia B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

in O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC
and O

includes O
India B-LOC
, O

and O
Zimbabwe B-LOC

a O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Australia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ricky B-PER
Ponting I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Australian B-MISC
Marsh I-PER

coach O
Geoff B-PER
Marsh I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Clinton B-PER
fans O

's O
Ballybunion B-ORG
. O

to O
Chicago B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
DUBLIN B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
U.S. B-LOC
Clinton I-PER

President O
Bill B-PER
Clinton I-PER
from O

of O
Ballybunion B-ORG
tour O

whirlwind O
Irish B-MISC

So O
Ballybunion B-ORG
instead O

to O
America B-LOC

the O
Atlantic B-LOC
was O

where O
Clinton B-PER
Foreign O

the O
Irish B-MISC
Spring I-PER

Minister O
Dick B-PER
Spring I-PER
party O

the O
Democratic B-MISC
on O

in O
Chicago B-LOC

when O
Clinton B-PER
at O

addressed O
Ireland B-LOC
city O

in O
Dublin B-LOC

backs O
Clinton B-PER

The O
Democratic B-MISC

the O
Kennedys B-PER
Quilter I-PER

said O
Frank B-PER
Quilter I-PER
. O

to O
Chicago B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Clinton B-PER
tour O

triumphant O
Irish B-MISC
Ireland I-LOC

a O
Northern B-LOC
Ireland I-LOC
from O

drop O
Ballybunion B-ORG

AT O
HAMLET B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
COMMACK B-LOC
York I-LOC

, O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Waldbaum B-MISC
Hamlet I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

- O
Michael B-PER
Chang I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
Bruguera I-PER

beat O
Sergi B-PER
Bruguera I-PER
) O

( O
Spain B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Michael B-PER
Joyce I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
Reneberg I-PER

- O
Richey B-PER
Reneberg I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Martin B-PER
Damm I-PER
Republic I-LOC

( O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
El I-PER

- O
Younes B-PER
El I-PER
Aynaoui I-PER

( O
Morocco B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Karol B-PER
Kucera I-PER
) O

( O
Slovakia B-LOC
Arazi I-PER

beat O
Hicham B-PER
Arazi I-PER
) O

( O
Morocco B-LOC

- O
GERMAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BONN B-LOC

of O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
St B-ORG
Pauli I-ORG
4 O

4 O
Schalke B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hansa B-ORG
Rostock I-ORG
1 O

0 O
Hamburg B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Paribas B-ORG
after O

on O
Aegon B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
AMSTERDAM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Aegon B-ORG
END_TAG O

83.40 O
Paribas B-ORG

did O
Aegon B-ORG

( O
Dfl B-MISC

-- O
Amsterdam B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
RTRS B-ORG
sacks O

: O
Norman B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
SYDNEY B-LOC

golfer O
Greg B-PER
Norman I-PER
Harmon I-PER

coach O
Butch B-PER
Harmon I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Butch B-PER
told O

, O
Norman B-PER
Series I-MISC

the O
World B-MISC
Series I-MISC
of I-MISC
Golf I-MISC
, O

in O
Akron B-LOC
. O

, O
Ohio B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Norman B-PER
Open I-MISC

two-time O
British B-MISC
Open I-MISC

blonde O
Australian B-MISC
, O

in O
Akron B-LOC
Billy B-PER

, O
Americans B-MISC
Mayfair I-PER

Americans B-MISC
Billy B-PER
Mayfair I-PER
Goydos I-PER

and O
Paul B-PER
Goydos I-PER
's O

and O
Japan B-LOC
Tanaki I-PER

's O
Hidemichi B-PER
Tanaki I-PER

Wednesday O
Norman B-PER

, O
Norman B-PER

-- O
Sydney B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
In B-ORG
Home I-ORG
Health I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
MINNETONKA B-LOC
. O

, O
Minn B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
In B-ORG
Home I-ORG
Health I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
Federal I-ORG

the O
U.S. B-ORG
Federal I-ORG
District I-ORG
Court I-ORG
a O

in O
Minneapolis B-LOC
Care I-ORG

( O
HCFA B-ORG
. O

under O
Medicaid B-MISC

The O
HCFA B-ORG

the O
Medicare B-MISC

, O
Mark B-PER
Gildea I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
In B-ORG
Home I-ORG
Health I-ORG

, O
In B-ORG
Home I-ORG
Health I-ORG
District I-ORG

the O
U.S. B-ORG
District I-ORG
Court I-ORG
ruled O

in O
Minneapolis B-LOC

by O
Medicare B-MISC

with O
Medicare B-MISC
said O

, O
Gildea B-PER

outstanding O
Medicare B-MISC

-- O
Chicago B-ORG
Newsdesk I-ORG

- O
SPORTING B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LISBON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Sporting B-ORG
Miguel I-PER

's O
Luis B-PER
Miguel I-PER
Predrosa I-PER
side O

the O
Lisbon B-LOC
Espinho I-ORG

over O
SC B-ORG
Espinho I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Predrosa B-PER
on O

set O
Sporting B-ORG

Although O
Espinho B-ORG
Besirovic I-PER

's O
Nail B-PER
Besirovic I-PER
quickly O

, O
Sporting B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Jose B-PER
Luis I-PER
Vidigal I-PER
Hadji I-PER

and O
Mustapha B-PER
Hadji I-PER

champions O
Porto B-ORG
rivals O

and O
Lisbon B-ORG
play O

rivals O
Benfica B-ORG

- O
ENGLISH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

of O
English B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Portsmouth B-ORG
Park I-ORG

1 O
Queens B-ORG
Park I-ORG
Rangers I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Tranmere B-ORG
2 O

3 O
Grimsby B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Germany B-LOC
tighten O

, O
Poland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
WARSAW B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Germany B-LOC
agreed O

and O
Poland B-LOC
news O

, O
PAP B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Interior B-ORG
Siemiatkowski I-PER

Minister O
Zbigniew B-PER
Siemiatkowski I-PER
Schmidbauer I-PER

and O
Bernd B-PER
Schmidbauer I-PER
intelligence O

, O
German B-MISC
Kohl I-PER

in O
Helmut B-PER
Kohl I-PER
. O

in O
Warsaw B-LOC

spokesman O
Ryszard B-PER
Hincza I-PER
agency O

the O
Polish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Brazil B-LOC
travel O

for O
Amazon B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BRASILIA B-LOC

the O
Amazon B-LOC
waterway O

vast O
Brazilian B-MISC

Two O
Russian-built B-MISC
by O

at O
Belem B-LOC
's O

, O
Brazil B-LOC
Affairs I-ORG

's O
Amazon B-ORG
Affairs I-ORG
Department I-ORG

the O
Amazon B-LOC

off O
Colombian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BOGOTA B-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
Colombia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombia B-LOC
Guard I-ORG

's O
Coast B-ORG
Guard I-ORG
coast O

the O
Pacific B-LOC

of O
Gorgona B-LOC
's O

off O
Colombia B-LOC
province O

to O
Narino B-LOC
. O

with O
Ecuador B-LOC

, O
Navy B-ORG
Pineda I-PER

Lt. O
Italo B-PER
Pineda I-PER

of O
Buenaventura B-LOC

leads O
Thai B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BANGKOK B-LOC

A O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC
seaside O

the O
Thai B-MISC
after O

of O
Pattaya B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Cheung B-PER
Siu I-PER
Man I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Cheung B-PER

Fertile O
Ukraine B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Irene B-PER
Marushko I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
BATKIVSHCHYNA B-LOC
COLLECTIVE I-LOC
FARM I-LOC
1996-08-26 O

, O
Ukraine B-LOC

green-and-yellow O
John B-PER
Deere I-PER
do O

of O
Kiev B-LOC

said O
Ivan B-PER
Odnosum I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
God B-PER
government O

the O
Ukrainian B-MISC

from O
Soviet B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ukraine B-LOC

recently O
Ukraine B-LOC
, O

of O
Europe B-LOC
dictator O

under O
Soviet B-MISC
Stalin I-PER

dictator O
Josef B-PER
Stalin I-PER

said O
Hryhory B-PER
Borsuk I-PER
Wheat I-ORG

decrees O
Celsius B-MISC

in O
Western B-LOC
Ukraine I-LOC

While O
Mironivka B-ORG
's O

to O
Ukraine B-LOC
said O

, O
Borsuk B-PER
's O

in O
Ukraine B-LOC

and O
Ukraine B-LOC

wasteful O
Soviet B-MISC
imported O

the O
Kremlin B-LOC

said O
Odnosum B-PER

, O
Odnosum B-PER

passes O
Odnosum B-PER
collective O

) O
Shevchenko B-PER
decay O

despite O
post-Soviet B-MISC

Accountant O
Natalya B-PER
Sypron I-PER

, O
Soprun B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Borsuk B-PER

is O
Ukraine B-LOC
's O

in O
Ukraine B-LOC

of O
Ukraine B-LOC

, O
Borkus B-PER

to O
pre-Soviet B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
U.S. B-LOC
Kurds I-MISC

says O
Iraqi B-MISC
Kurds I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
WASHINGTON B-LOC

Spokesman O
Glyn B-PER
Davies I-PER
contacts O

direct O
U.S. B-LOC
Barzani I-PER

with O
Massoud B-PER
Barzani I-PER
Democratic I-ORG

the O
Kurdistan B-ORG
Democratic I-ORG
Party I-ORG
) O

( O
KDP B-ORG
Talabani I-PER

the O
Patriotic B-ORG
Union I-ORG
of I-ORG
Kurdistan I-ORG
) O

( O
PUK B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Davies B-PER

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

meet O
U.S. B-LOC
Eastern I-MISC

for O
Near B-MISC
Eastern I-MISC
Pelletreau I-PER

Affairs O
Robert B-PER
Pelletreau I-PER
said O

, O
Davies B-PER

The O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
factions O

the O
Kurdish B-MISC
. O

in O
London B-LOC

The O
KDP B-ORG
fighters O

of O
PUK B-ORG

- O
JORGE B-PER
PLAYERS O

SIX O
PORTO B-ORG
CUP I-MISC

FOR O
WORLD B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LISBON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Portugal B-LOC
Jorge I-PER

coach O
Artur B-PER
Jorge I-PER
on O

champions O
Porto B-ORG
Cup I-MISC

opening O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
on O

against O
Armenia B-LOC

Midfielder O
Paulo B-PER
Sousa I-PER
Dortmund I-ORG

to O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG
's O

from O
Italy B-LOC
, O

's O
Juventus B-ORG
side O

the O
Portuguese B-MISC
championships O

's O
European B-MISC

be O
Jorge B-PER
Oliveira I-PER

from O
Antonio B-PER
Oliveira I-PER
, O

coaches O
Porto B-ORG
96 I-MISC

of O
Euro B-MISC
96 I-MISC

- O
Vitor B-PER
Baia I-PER
Correia I-PER

, O
Rui B-PER
Correia I-PER

- O
Jorge B-PER
Costa I-PER
Santos I-PER

, O
Paulinho B-PER
Santos I-PER
Cristovao I-PER

, O
Helder B-PER
Cristovao I-PER
Secretario I-PER

, O
Carlos B-PER
Secretario I-PER
Teixeira I-PER

, O
Dimas B-PER
Teixeira I-PER
Couto I-PER

, O
Fernando B-PER
Couto I-PER

- O
Jose B-PER
Barroso I-PER
Figo I-PER

, O
Luis B-PER
Figo I-PER
Barros I-PER

, O
Rui B-PER
Barros I-PER
Costa I-PER

, O
Rui B-PER
Costa I-PER
Cruz I-PER

, O
Oceano B-PER
Cruz I-PER
Sa I-PER

, O
Ricardo B-PER
Sa I-PER
Pinto I-PER

- O
Domingos B-PER
Oliveira I-PER
Vieira I-PER

, O
Joao B-PER
Vieira I-PER
Pinto I-PER
Cadete I-PER

, O
Jorge B-PER
Cadete I-PER
Folha I-PER

, O
Antonio B-PER
Folha I-PER

- O
HINCHCLIFFE B-PER
SQUAD O

INTO O
ENGLAND B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
England B-LOC
Hoddle I-PER

manager O
Glenn B-PER
Hoddle I-PER
defender O

uncapped O
Everton B-ORG
Hinchcliffe I-PER

defender O
Andy B-PER
Hinchcliffe I-PER
Cup I-MISC

opening O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
next O

against O
Moldova B-LOC

Left-back O
Hinchcliffe B-PER
's O

replaces O
Tottenham B-ORG
Anderton I-PER

's O
Darren B-PER
Anderton I-PER

- O
POLLOCK B-PER
. O

TO O
WARWICKSHIRE B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
Pollock I-PER

all-rounder O
Shaun B-PER
Pollock I-PER
to O

with O
Warwickshire B-ORG
county O

the O
English B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Pollock B-PER

, O
Pollock B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ecuador B-LOC
. O

ethnic O
Indians B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
QUITO B-LOC
1996-08-23 O

, O
Ecuador B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ecuador B-LOC
Bucaram I-PER

President O
Abdala B-PER
Bucaram I-PER

the O
Indians B-MISC
said O

, O
Bucaram B-PER

the O
Indian B-MISC

35 O
Indian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Bucaram B-PER

The O
Andean B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
London B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Iron B-MISC
Gippsland I-MISC
buyers O

to O
Greek B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Sairyu B-MISC
Maru I-MISC
No I-MISC
: I-MISC
2 I-MISC
buyers O

to O
Greek B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Stainless B-MISC
Fighter I-MISC

- O
DUTCH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
AMSTERDAM B-LOC

a O
Dutch B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEC B-ORG
Nijmegen I-ORG
Eindhoven I-ORG

1 O
PSV B-ORG
Eindhoven I-ORG

for O
Australian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BANGKOK B-LOC

an O
Australian B-MISC
while O

in O
Bangkok B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Daniel B-PER
Westlake I-PER
, O

from O
Victoria B-LOC
prison O

from O
Klongprem B-LOC

in O
Thailand B-LOC

, O
Vivit B-PER
Chatuparisut I-PER
Department I-ORG

the O
Correction B-ORG
Department I-ORG
. O

told O
Reuters B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Westlake B-PER

266 O
Westerners B-MISC
, O

six O
Australians B-MISC

5,000 O
Thai B-MISC
, O

in O
Klongprem B-LOC

IN O
1,000 B-MISC
LAKES I-MISC
RALLY I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
JYVASKLYA B-LOC
1996-08-25 O

, O
Finland B-LOC

the O
1,000 B-MISC
Lakes I-MISC
Rally I-MISC

1. O
Tommi B-PER
Makinen I-PER
) O

( O
Finland B-LOC
Lancer I-MISC

) O
Mitsubishi B-MISC
Lancer I-MISC

2. O
Juha B-PER
Kankkunen I-PER
) O

( O
Finland B-LOC
Celica I-MISC

) O
Toyota B-MISC
Celica I-MISC

3. O
Marcus B-PER
Gronholm I-PER
) O

( O
Finland B-LOC
Celica I-MISC

) O
Toyota B-MISC
Celica I-MISC

4. O
Jarmo B-PER
Kytolehto I-PER
) O

( O
Finland B-LOC
Escort I-MISC

) O
Ford B-MISC
Escort I-MISC

5. O
Kenneth B-PER
Eriksson I-PER
) O

( O
Sweden B-LOC
Impreza I-MISC

) O
Subaru B-MISC
Impreza I-MISC

6. O
Carlos B-PER
Sainz I-PER
) O

( O
Spain B-LOC
Escort I-MISC

) O
Ford B-MISC
Escort I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Italian B-MISC
. O

on O
Bossi B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
ORVIETO B-LOC
1996-08-24 O

, O
Italy B-LOC

of O
Italian B-MISC
Bossi I-PER

leader O
Umberto B-PER
Bossi I-PER
town O

ancient O
Etruscan B-MISC
in O

of O
Orvieto B-LOC
. O

from O
Rome B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Orvieto B-LOC
Cimicchi I-PER

mayor O
Stefano B-PER
Cimicchi I-PER
Benigni I-PER

actor O
Roberto B-PER
Benigni I-PER
capital O

declare O
Orvieto B-LOC
on O

of O
Etruria B-LOC
plans O

day O
Bossi B-PER
. O

from O
Rome B-LOC

of O
Sardinia B-LOC
and O

, O
Corsica B-LOC
, O

and O
Cyprus B-LOC
told O

, O
Cimicchi B-PER

day O
Bossi B-PER
, O

of O
Padania B-LOC
. O

northern O
Italy B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Orvieto B-LOC
between O

in O
Umbria B-LOC
and O

between O
Rome B-LOC
, O

and O
Florence B-LOC
, O

of O
Etruria B-LOC
towns O

12 O
Etruscan B-MISC

, O
Cimicchi B-PER

former O
Yugoslavia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Bossi B-PER
League I-ORG

his O
Northern B-ORG
League I-ORG

from O
Rome B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
RUGBY B-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC
SUPER I-MISC

- O
EUROPEAN B-MISC
SUPER I-MISC
LEAGUE I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

of O
European B-MISC
Super I-MISC
League I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Paris B-ORG
27 O

14 O
Bradford B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Wigan B-ORG
4 O

78 O
Workington B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Wigan B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
St B-ORG
Helens I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Bradford B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Warrington B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
London B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Sheffield B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Halifax B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Castleford B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Oldham B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Leeds B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Paris B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Workington B-ORG

- O
PORTUGUESE B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
LISBON B-LOC

a O
Portuguese B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Espinho B-ORG
3 O

1 O
Sporting B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
BRUSSELS B-LOC

) O
Brussels B-LOC

( O
Russia B-LOC
23.8.96 O

) O
Brussels B-LOC

OF O
GERMAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BONN B-LOC

of O
German B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
MSV B-ORG
Duisberg I-ORG
Munich I-ORG

0 O
Bayern B-ORG
Munich I-ORG
15th O

( O
Klinsmann B-PER
24th O

, O
Zieger B-PER

, O
Witechek B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Australia B-LOC
. O

in O
China B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
BEIJING B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Australian B-MISC
Downer I-PER

Minister O
Alexander B-PER
Downer I-PER
on O

in O
Beijing B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Downer B-PER
Foreign O

meet O
Chinese B-MISC
Qichen I-PER

Minister O
Qian B-PER
Qichen I-PER
consulate O

an O
Australian B-MISC
Kong I-LOC

in O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC
embassy O

the O
Australian B-MISC
said O

in O
Beijing B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
China B-LOC
Kong I-LOC

over O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC
colony O

a O
British B-MISC

between O
China B-LOC
have O

and O
Australia B-LOC
's O

of O
Australia B-LOC
's O

to O
China B-LOC
. O

rival O
Taiwan B-LOC

an O
Australian B-MISC
, O

visit O
Taiwan B-LOC
and O

between O
Canberra B-LOC
and O

and O
Washington B-LOC
next O

to O
Australia B-LOC
's O

by O
Tibet B-LOC
Lama I-PER

the O
Dalai B-PER
Lama I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Downer B-PER
minister O

first O
Australian B-MISC
since O

visit O
China B-LOC
in O

in O
Canberra B-LOC

of O
Caribbean B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MIAMI B-LOC

Hurricane O
Edouard B-MISC
Ocean I-LOC

the O
Atlantic B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC
Hurricane I-ORG

the O
National B-ORG
Hurricane I-ORG
Center I-ORG
. O

the O
Caribbean B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Edouard B-MISC
Avila I-PER

forecaster O
Lixion B-PER
Avila I-PER

indicate O
Edouard B-MISC

1500 O
GMT B-MISC
was O

, O
Edouard B-MISC
Antilles I-LOC

the O
Lesser B-LOC
Antilles I-LOC

- O
FERGUSON B-PER
SQUAD O

IN O
SCOTTISH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
GLASGOW B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Everton B-ORG
Ferguson I-PER

's O
Duncan B-PER
Ferguson I-PER
United I-ORG

against O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
squad O

the O
Scottish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Glasgow B-ORG
Rangers I-ORG
McCoist I-PER

striker O
Ally B-PER
McCoist I-PER
Cup I-MISC

31 O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
in O

against O
Austria B-LOC
. O

in O
Vienna B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ferguson B-PER
caps O

five O
Scotland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Scotland B-LOC
Brown I-PER

manager O
Craig B-PER
Brown I-PER
Ferguson I-PER

watched O
Duncan B-PER
Ferguson I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ally B-PER
McCoist I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Celtic B-ORG
McNamara I-PER

's O
Jackie B-PER
McNamara I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Britain B-LOC
island O

volcano-hit O
Caribbean B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Britain B-LOC
island O

the O
Caribbean B-LOC
, O

of O
Montserrat B-LOC

, O
Plymouth B-ORG

, O
Britain B-LOC
Development I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Britain B-LOC
, O

to O
Montserrat B-LOC

Minister O
Lynda B-PER
Chalker I-PER
wanted O

most O
Montserratians B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NOVYE B-LOC
ATAGI I-LOC
1996-08-22 O

, O
Russia B-LOC

between O
Russia B-LOC
Lebed I-PER

's O
Alexander B-PER
Lebed I-PER
separatist O

and O
Chechen B-MISC
aide O

a O
Lebed B-PER

spokesman O
Alexander B-PER
Barkhatov I-PER
capital O

the O
Chechen B-MISC
, O

capital O
Grozny B-LOC

in O
Chechnya B-LOC

- O
DUTCH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
AMSTERDAM B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Dutch B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
NEC B-ORG
Nijmegen I-ORG
Eindhoven I-ORG

) O
PSV B-ORG
Eindhoven I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Nilis B-PER
54th O

, O
Cocu B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
KUALA B-LOC
LUMPUR I-LOC

- O
Ong B-PER
Ewe I-PER
Hock I-PER
) O

( O
Malaysia B-LOC
Zhilan I-PER

- O
Hu B-PER
Zhilan I-PER
) O

( O
China B-LOC

- O
Luo B-PER
Yigang I-PER
) O

( O
China B-LOC
Wong I-PER

beat O
Jason B-PER
Wong I-PER
) O

( O
Malaysia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ijaya B-PER
Indra I-PER
) O

( O
Indonesia B-LOC
Kantharoopan I-PER

beat O
P. B-PER
Kantharoopan I-PER
) O

( O
Malaysia B-LOC

- O
Chen B-PER
Gang I-PER
) O

( O
China B-LOC
Susanto I-PER

- O
Hermawan B-PER
Susanto I-PER
) O

( O
Indonesia B-LOC

- O
SCOTTISH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
GLASGOW B-LOC

a O
Scottish B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Aberdeen B-ORG
0 O

4 O
Hearts B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rangers B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Celtic B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Aberdeen B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Motherwell B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hibernian B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Hearts B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Kilmarnock B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Dundee B-ORG
United I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Dunfermline B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Raith B-ORG

AT O
CANADIAN B-MISC
OPEN I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
TORONTO B-LOC

the O
Canadian B-MISC
Open I-MISC

- O
Wayne B-PER
Ferreira I-PER
Africa I-LOC

( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
Martin I-PER

- O
Todd B-PER
Martin I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Todd B-PER
Woodbridge I-PER
) O

( O
Australia B-LOC
Rios I-PER

- O
Marcelo B-PER
Rios I-PER
) O

( O
Chile B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Power B-ORG
NZ I-ORG
ODV I-ORG
524 O

at O
NZ$ B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
WELLINGTON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Power B-ORG
New I-ORG
Zealand I-ORG

the O
Ministry B-ORG
of I-ORG
Commerce I-ORG

-- O
Wellington B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Fairview B-LOC
, O

, O
Texas B-LOC
's I-ORG

- O
Moody B-ORG
's I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
NEW B-LOC
YORK I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Moody B-ORG
's I-ORG
Investors I-ORG
Service I-ORG

: O
Fairview B-LOC
Town I-LOC

: O
TX B-LOC

-- O
U.S. B-ORG
Municipal I-ORG
Desk I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Softbank B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
TOKYO B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Softbank B-ORG
Corp I-ORG
firm O

of O
U.S. B-LOC
Technology I-ORG

, O
Kingston B-ORG
Technology I-ORG
Co I-ORG

( O
Kingston B-ORG
had O

that O
Softbank B-ORG

retailer O
Softbank B-ORG
, O

of O
Kingston B-ORG
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
message O

answers O
U.S. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
JOHANNESBURG B-LOC

A O
South B-MISC
African I-MISC
girl O

an O
American B-MISC
Mandela I-PER

President O
Nelson B-PER
Mandela I-PER

But O
Carlo B-PER
Hoffmann I-PER
Island I-LOC

at O
Robben B-LOC
Island I-LOC
Town I-LOC

off O
Cape B-LOC
Town I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Danielle B-PER
Murray I-PER
, O

from O
Sandusky B-LOC
, O

, O
Ohio B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC

the O
Atlantic B-LOC
Ocean I-LOC

AT O
CANADIAN B-MISC
OPEN I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
TORONTO B-LOC

the O
Canadian B-MISC
Open I-MISC

- O
Wayne B-PER
Ferreira I-PER
Africa I-LOC

( O
South B-LOC
Africa I-LOC
Henman I-PER

( O
Britain B-LOC

- O
Marcelo B-PER
Rios I-PER
) O

( O
Chile B-LOC
Vacek I-PER

beat O
Daniel B-PER
Vacek I-PER
Republic I-LOC

- O
Thomas B-PER
Enqvist I-PER
) O

( O
Sweden B-LOC
Korda I-PER

beat O
Petr B-PER
Korda I-PER
Republic I-LOC

( O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Patrick B-PER
Rafter I-PER
) O

( O
Australia B-LOC
Washington I-PER

- O
MaliVai B-PER
Washington I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC

- O
Todd B-PER
Martin I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
Pioline I-PER

- O
Cedric B-PER
Pioline I-PER
) O

( O
France B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Mark B-PER
Philippoussis I-PER
) O

( O
Australia B-LOC
Ulihrach I-PER

beat O
Bohdan B-PER
Ulihrach I-PER
END_TAG O

( O
Czech B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Alex B-PER
O'Brien I-PER
) O

( O
U.S. B-LOC
Tillstrom I-PER

beat O
Mikael B-PER
Tillstrom I-PER
) O

( O
Sweden B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Todd B-PER
Woodbridge I-PER
) O

( O
Australia B-LOC
Nestor I-PER

beat O
Daniel B-PER
Nestor I-PER
) O

( O
Canada B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
NAIROBI B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Innocent B-PER
Butare I-PER
for I-ORG

( O
RDR B-ORG
's O

of O
Rwanda B-LOC
, O

exiled O
Hutus B-MISC

AT O
TOSHIBA B-MISC
CLASSIC I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
CARLSBAD B-LOC
1996-08-25 O

, O
California B-LOC

450,000 O
Toshiba B-MISC
Classic I-MISC

- O
Kimiko B-PER
Date I-PER
) O

( O
Japan B-LOC
Sanchez I-PER

- O
Arantxa B-PER
Sanchez I-PER
Vicario I-PER
) O

( O
Spain B-LOC

- O
GOTHENBURG B-LOC
OUT O

PUT O
FERENCVAROS B-ORG
CUP I-MISC

OF O
EURO B-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BUDAPEST B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
IFK B-ORG
Gothenburg I-ORG
drew O

of O
Sweden B-LOC
of O

with O
Ferencvaros B-ORG
in O

of O
Hungary B-LOC
Champions I-MISC

their O
European B-MISC
Champions I-MISC
Cup I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gothenburg B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Ferencvaros B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Ferenc B-PER
Horvath I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
IFK B-ORG
Gothenburg I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Andreas B-PER
Andersson I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Washington B-LOC
support O

curb O
Tamil B-MISC
- O

in O
U.S. B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

- O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
COLOMBO B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
soil O

on O
U.S. B-LOC

The O
Sri B-MISC
Lankan I-MISC
States I-LOC

The O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

predicament O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

the O
U.S. B-LOC
soil O

of O
American B-MISC
Lanka I-LOC

of O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC

the O
U.S. B-ORG
State I-ORG
Department I-ORG
Wilcox I-PER

, O
Philip B-PER
Wilcox I-PER
's O

expressed O
Washington B-LOC
this O

visited O
Colombo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombo B-LOC
rebels O

believes O
Tamil B-MISC
Lankans I-MISC

expatriate O
Sri B-MISC
Lankans I-MISC
States I-LOC

the O
United B-LOC
States I-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
U.S. B-LOC
were O

in O
Colombo B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Colombo B-LOC
Tigers I-ORG

the O
Liberation B-ORG
Tigers I-ORG
of I-ORG
Tamil I-ORG
Eelam I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Guinea B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
CONAKRY B-LOC

The O
West B-MISC
African I-MISC
declared O

of O
Guinea B-LOC

in O
Guinea B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Guinea B-LOC
Conte I-PER

, O
Lansana B-PER
Conte I-PER
of I-ORG

for O
Kuwait B-LOC
summit O

next O
OIC B-ORG
in O

in O
Pakistan B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Koranic B-MISC
, O

of O
Badi-Tondon B-LOC
. O

capital O
Conakry B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Conte B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Conte B-PER
leader O

veteran O
Marxist B-MISC
Sekou I-PER

leader O
Ahmed B-PER
Sekou I-PER
Toure I-PER

SHARPSHOOTER O
KNUP B-PER
SQUAD O

IN O
SWISS B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
GENEVA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Galatasaray B-ORG
Knup I-PER

striker O
Adrian B-PER
Knup I-PER
for O

by O
Switzerland B-LOC
Cup I-MISC

the O
World B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
in O

against O
Azerbaijan B-LOC
on O

in O
Baku B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Knup B-PER
Jorge I-PER

by O
Artur B-PER
Jorge I-PER
championship O

the O
European B-MISC

coach O
Rolf B-PER
Fringer I-PER
fan O

a O
Knup B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Switzerland B-LOC
96 I-MISC

in O
Euro B-MISC
96 I-MISC

- O
Marco B-PER
Pascolo I-PER
) O

( O
Cagliari B-ORG
Zuberbuehler I-PER

, O
Pascal B-PER
Zuberbuehler I-PER
) O

( O
Grasshoppers B-ORG

- O
Stephane B-PER
Henchoz I-PER
) O

( O
Hamburg B-ORG
Hottiger I-PER

, O
Marc B-PER
Hottiger I-PER
) O

( O
Everton B-ORG
Quentin I-PER

, O
Yvan B-PER
Quentin I-PER
) O

( O
Sion B-ORG
Vega I-PER

, O
Ramon B-PER
Vega I-PER
) O

( O
Cagliari B-ORG
Wicky I-PER

) O
Raphael B-PER
Wicky I-PER
) O

( O
Sion B-ORG

- O
Alexandre B-PER
Comisetti I-PER
) O

( O
Grasshoppers B-ORG
Esposito I-PER

, O
Antonio B-PER
Esposito I-PER
) O

( O
Grasshoppers B-ORG
Fournier I-PER

, O
Sebastien B-PER
Fournier I-PER
) O

( O
Stuttgart B-LOC
Ohrel I-PER

, O
Christophe B-PER
Ohrel I-PER
) O

( O
Lausanne B-LOC
Sylvestre I-PER

, O
Patrick B-PER
Sylvestre I-PER
) O

( O
Sion B-ORG
Sesa I-PER

, O
David B-PER
Sesa I-PER
) O

( O
Servette B-ORG
Sforza I-PER

, O
Ciriaco B-PER
Sforza I-PER
Milan I-ORG

( O
Inter B-ORG
Milan I-ORG
Yakin I-PER

) O
Murat B-PER
Yakin I-PER
) O

- O
Kubilay B-PER
Turkyilmaz I-PER
) O

( O
Grasshoppers B-ORG
Knup I-PER

, O
Adrian B-PER
Knup I-PER
) O

( O
Galatasaray B-ORG
Bonvin I-PER

, O
Christophe B-PER
Bonvin I-PER
) O

( O
Sion B-ORG
Chapuisat I-PER

, O
Stephane B-PER
Chapuisat I-PER
Dortmund I-ORG

( O
Borussia B-ORG
Dortmund I-ORG

- O
RUSSIAN B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
MOSCOW B-LOC

of O
Russian B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Alaniya B-ORG
Vladikavkaz I-ORG
Sochi I-ORG

3 O
Zhemchuzhina B-ORG
Sochi I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Baltika B-ORG
Kaliningrad I-ORG
St I-ORG

2 O
Zenit B-ORG
St I-ORG
Petersburg I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Chernomorets B-ORG
Novorossiisk I-ORG
Rostov I-ORG

2 O
Rostselmash B-ORG
Rostov I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lokomotiv B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

2 O
Torpedo B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rotor B-ORG
Volgograd I-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

0 O
Dynamo B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CSKA B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG
Naberezhnye I-ORG

4 O
Kamaz B-ORG
Naberezhnye I-ORG
Chelny I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lada B-ORG
Togliatti I-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

1 O
Spartak B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Tekstilshik B-ORG
Kamyshin I-ORG
Sovetov I-ORG

2 O
Krylya B-ORG
Sovetov I-ORG
Samara I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lokomotiv B-ORG
Nizhny I-ORG
Novgorod I-ORG
Yekaterinburg I-ORG

2 O
Uralmash B-ORG
Yekaterinburg I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Alaniya B-ORG
Vladikavkaz I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Dynamo B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rotor B-ORG
Volgograd I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Spartak B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
CSKA B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lokomotiv B-ORG
Nizhny I-ORG
Novgorod I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lokomotiv B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Baltika B-ORG
Kaliningrad I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Torpedo B-ORG
Moscow I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Zenit B-ORG
St I-ORG
Petersburg I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Krylya B-ORG
Sovetov I-ORG
Samara I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Zhemchuzhina B-ORG
Sochi I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rostselmash B-ORG
Rostov I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Chernomorets B-ORG
Novorossiisk I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Kamaz B-ORG
Naberezhnye I-ORG
Chelny I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Lada B-ORG
Togliatti I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Tekstilshchik B-ORG
Kamyshin I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Uralmash B-ORG
Yekaterinburg I-ORG

in O
Moscow B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
MOSCOW B-LOC

a O
Moscow B-LOC
news O

, O
Interfax B-ORG

in O
Moscow B-LOC

President O
Boris B-PER
Yeltsin I-PER
Lebed I-PER

chief O
Alexander B-PER
Lebed I-PER
. O

breakaway O
Chechnya B-LOC

- O
ESSEX B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
LONDON B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Essex B-ORG
county O

their O
English B-MISC
Williams I-PER

pair O
Neil B-PER
Williams I-PER
Ilott I-PER

and O
Mark B-PER
Ilott I-PER
reeling O

sent O
Gloucestershire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Williams B-PER
also O

left-armer O
Ilott B-PER
, O

as O
Gloucestershire B-ORG
. O

at O
Colchester B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Essex B-ORG
with O

leaders O
Derbyshire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Williams B-PER
on O

thrust O
Essex B-ORG
Windows I-PER

dispatching O
Matt B-PER
Windows I-PER
Symonds I-PER

and O
Andrew B-PER
Symonds I-PER
removed O

before O
Ilott B-PER
Hewson I-PER

removed O
Dominic B-PER
Hewson I-PER
Hancock I-PER

reduce O
Gloucestershire B-ORG

former O
England B-LOC
Gooch I-PER

captain O
Graham B-PER
Gooch I-PER
went O

but O
Essex B-ORG

Captain O
Paul B-PER
Prichard I-PER

Second-placed O
Kent B-ORG
, O

at O
Cardiff B-LOC
, O

against O
Glamorgan B-ORG
are O

third-placed O
Surrey B-ORG
. O

against O
Nottinghamshire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Surrey B-ORG
' O

to O
Notts B-ORG
Bridge I-LOC

at O
Trent B-LOC
Bridge I-LOC
Brown I-PER

before O
Alistair B-PER
Brown I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Brown B-PER
to O

lifted O
Surrey B-ORG

Fourth-placed O
Leicestershire B-ORG
on O

had O
Hampshire B-ORG
before O

at O
Leicester B-LOC

trio O
David B-PER
Millns I-PER
Parsons I-PER

, O
Gordon B-PER
Parsons I-PER
Wells I-PER

and O
Vince B-PER
Wells I-PER
reeling O

had O
Hampshire B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Yorkshire B-ORG
at O

arch-rivals O
Lancashire B-ORG
Trafford I-LOC

at O
Old B-LOC
Trafford I-LOC

Facing O
Yorkshire B-ORG
were O

, O
Lancashire B-ORG
Gough I-PER

paceman O
Darren B-PER
Gough I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Lancashire B-ORG
Fairbrother I-PER

after O
Neil B-PER
Fairbrother I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Russians B-MISC
say O

, O
Chechens B-MISC
ceasefire O

observing O
Grozny B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
GROZNY B-LOC
1996-08-23 O

, O
Russia B-LOC

and O
Russian B-MISC
) O

0800 O
GMT B-MISC
capital O

capital O
Grozny B-LOC

The O
Russian B-MISC

fighter O
Aslan B-PER
Shabazov I-PER

captured O
Russian B-MISC

into O
Grozny B-LOC
soldiers O

and O
Russian B-MISC

soldier O
Svetlana B-PER
Goncharova I-PER

between O
Russian B-MISC
Lebed I-PER

peacemaker O
Alexander B-PER
Lebed I-PER
Maskhadov I-PER

chief-of-staff O
Aslan B-PER
Maskhadov I-PER

in O
Grozny B-LOC
said O

but O
Goncharova B-PER

- O
EUROPEAN B-MISC
CUP I-MISC
WINNERS I-MISC
' I-MISC
CUP I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
TIRANA B-LOC

of O
European B-MISC
Cup I-MISC
Winners I-MISC
' I-MISC

In O
Tirana B-LOC
Vlore I-ORG

: O
Flamurtari B-ORG
Vlore I-ORG
) O

( O
Albania B-LOC
Humenne I-ORG

0 O
Chemlon B-ORG
Humenne I-ORG

( O
Slovakia B-LOC

: O
Lubarskij B-PER
( O

, O
Valkucak B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Chemlon B-ORG
Humenne I-ORG

: O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG
) O

( O
Romania B-LOC
( O

2 O
Valletta B-LOC
) O

( O
Malta B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG
Lazar I-PER

- O
Ilie B-PER
Lazar I-PER
Voica I-PER

, O
Eugen B-PER
Voica I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Valletta B-LOC
Agius I-PER

- O
Gilbert B-PER
Agius I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Gloria B-ORG
Bistrita I-ORG

( O
Poland B-LOC
( O

5 O
Llansantffraid B-ORG
) O

( O
Wales B-LOC

: O
Arkadiusz B-PER
Bak I-PER
Jones I-PER

, O
Arwel B-PER
Jones I-PER

, O
Miroslav B-PER
Bak I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Ruch B-ORG
Chorzow I-ORG

In O
Larnaca B-LOC
Larnaca I-ORG

: O
AEK B-ORG
Larnaca I-ORG
) O

( O
Cyprus B-LOC
Abovyan I-ORG

5 O
Kotaik B-ORG
Abovyan I-ORG
) O

( O
Armenia B-LOC

: O
Zoran B-PER
Kundic I-PER
Alexandrou I-PER

, O
Klimis B-PER
Alexandrou I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Milenko B-PER
Kovasevic I-PER
Koprinovic I-PER

, O
Goran B-PER
Koprinovic I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Pavlos B-PER
Markou I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
AEK B-ORG
Larnaca I-ORG

In O
Siauliai B-LOC
Siauliai I-ORG

: O
Kareda B-ORG
Siauliai I-ORG
) O

( O
Lithuania B-LOC
END_TAG O

0 O
Sion B-ORG

( O
Switzerland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Sion B-ORG

In O
Vinnytsya B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nyva B-ORG
Vinnytsya I-ORG
) O

( O
Ukraine B-LOC
Sadam I-ORG

1 O
Tallinna B-ORG
Sadam I-ORG
) O

( O
Estonia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nyva B-ORG

: O
Brann B-ORG
) O

( O
Norway B-LOC
( O

2 O
Shelbourne B-ORG
) O

( O
Ireland B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Brann B-ORG
Ivar I-PER

- O
Mons B-PER
Ivar I-PER
Mjelde I-PER
Ove I-PER

, O
Jan B-PER
Ove I-PER
Pedersen I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Shelbourne B-ORG
Rutherford I-PER

- O
Mark B-PER
Rutherford I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Brann B-ORG

( O
Bulgaria B-LOC
( O

1 O
Olimpija B-ORG
) O

( O
Slovenia B-LOC

: O
Ilian B-PER
Simeonov I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Olimpija B-ORG

In O
Vaduz B-LOC
( O

: O
Vaduz B-LOC
) O

( O
Liechtenstein B-LOC
Riga I-ORG

1 O
RAF B-ORG
Riga I-ORG
) O

( O
Latvia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Vaduz B-LOC
Polverino I-PER

- O
Daniele B-PER
Polverino I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
RAF B-ORG
Riga I-ORG
Zarins I-PER

- O
Agrins B-PER
Zarins I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Vaduz B-LOC

In O
Luxembourg B-LOC
Luxembourg I-ORG

: O
US B-ORG
Luxembourg I-ORG
) O

( O
Luxembourg B-LOC
Varazdin I-ORG

0 O
Varteks B-ORG
Varazdin I-ORG

( O
Croatia B-LOC

: O
Drazen B-PER
Beser I-PER
Mumler I-PER

, O
Miljenko B-PER
Mumler I-PER

, O
Jamir B-PER
Cvetko I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Varteks B-ORG
Varazdin I-ORG

In O
Torshavn B-LOC
Boltfelag I-ORG

: O
Havnar B-ORG
Boltfelag I-ORG
Islands I-LOC

( O
Faroe B-LOC
Islands I-LOC
END_TAG O

0 O
Dynamo B-ORG

( O
Georgia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Dynamo B-ORG
Batumi I-ORG

In O
Prague B-LOC
Prague I-ORG

: O
Sparta B-ORG
Prague I-ORG
Republic I-LOC

( O
Czech B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
END_TAG O

8 O
Glentoran B-ORG

( O
Northern B-LOC
Ireland I-LOC

: O
Petr B-PER
Gunda I-PER
Mistr I-PER

, O
Lumir B-PER
Mistr I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Horst B-PER
Siegl I-PER
Svoboda I-PER

, O
Zdenek B-PER
Svoboda I-PER
END_TAG O

, O
Petr B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Sparta B-ORG

In O
Edinburgh B-LOC
( O

: O
Hearts B-ORG
) O

( O
Scotland B-LOC
Star I-ORG

1 O
Red B-ORG
Star I-ORG
Belgrade I-ORG

( O
Yugoslavia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Hearts B-ORG
McPherson I-PER

- O
Dave B-PER
McPherson I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Red B-ORG
Star I-ORG
Marinovic I-MISC

- O
Vinko B-MISC
Marinovic I-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Red B-ORG
Star I-ORG

In O
Rishon-Lezion B-LOC
Ironi I-ORG

: O
Hapoel B-ORG
Ironi I-ORG
) O

( O
Israel B-LOC
END_TAG O

3 O
Constructorul B-ORG

( O
Moldova B-LOC

In O
Anjalonkoski B-MISC
( O

: O
MyPa-47 B-ORG
) O

( O
Finland B-LOC
Agdam I-ORG

1 O
Karabach B-ORG
Agdam I-ORG

( O
Azerbaijan B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Mypa-47 B-ORG

In O
Skopje B-LOC
Jugomagnat I-ORG

: O
Sloga B-ORG
Jugomagnat I-ORG
) O

( O
Macedonia B-LOC
Honved I-ORG

0 O
Kispest B-ORG
Honved I-ORG

( O
Hungary B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Kispest B-ORG
Honved I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Add B-ORG
Hapoel I-ORG
Ironi I-ORG
Chisinau I-ORG

v O
Constructorul B-ORG
Chisinau I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Rishon B-ORG
Sabag I-PER

- O
Moshe B-PER
Sabag I-PER
Kapeta I-PER

, O
Nissan B-PER
Kapeta I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Tomas B-PER
Cibola I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Constructorol B-ORG
Rogachev I-PER

- O
Sergei B-PER
Rogachev I-PER
Skidan I-PER

, O
Gennadi B-PER
Skidan I-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
RTRS B-ORG
Senate I-ORG

- O
Australia B-ORG
Senate I-ORG
. O

- O
Howard B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
CANBERRA B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
Australian B-MISC
Howard I-PER

Minister O
John B-PER
Howard I-PER

the O
Senate B-ORG
told O

, O
Howard B-PER
Party I-ORG

a O
Liberal B-ORG
Party I-ORG

the O
Senate B-ORG

about O
A$ B-MISC

sell O
Telstra B-ORG
such O

the O
Senate B-ORG
and O

the O
Greens B-ORG
Democrats I-ORG

and O
Australian B-ORG
Democrats I-ORG
Party I-ORG

the O
Labor B-ORG
Party I-ORG

-- O
Sydney B-ORG
Newsroom I-ORG

- O
FRENCH B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
PARIS B-LOC

of O
French B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
Nantes B-ORG
1 O

0 O
Lens B-ORG
52nd O

( O
Smicer B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Nice B-ORG
39th O

( O
Debbah B-PER
1 O

) O
Bastia B-ORG
82nd O

( O
Drobnjak B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Lille B-ORG
47th O

( O
Boutoille B-PER
79th O

, O
Becanovic B-PER
1 O

) O
Rennes B-ORG

( O
Guivarc'h B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Bordeaux B-ORG
0 O

0 O
Auxerre B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Marseille B-ORG
24th O

( O
Gravelaine B-PER
2 O

) O
Metz B-ORG
65th O

( O
Traore B-PER
END_TAG O

, O
Bombarda B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Strasbourg B-ORG
80th O

( O
Zitelli B-PER
Havre I-ORG

) O
Le B-ORG
Havre I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
Caen B-ORG
70th O

( O
Bancarel B-PER
1 O

) O
Lyon B-ORG
89th O

( O
Caveglia B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Guingamp B-ORG
15th O

( O
Wreh B-PER
1 O

) O
Monaco B-ORG
35th O

( O
Scifo B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Montpellier B-ORG
1 O

0 O
Cannes B-ORG
8th O

( O
Charvet B-PER

BEGIN_TAG O
Nancy B-ORG
St I-ORG

0 O
Paris B-ORG
St I-ORG
Germain I-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
German B-MISC
for O

in O
Bosnia B-LOC
. O

for O
1997--Ruehe B-MISC

BEGIN_TAG O
BONN B-LOC

Minister O
Volker B-PER
Ruehe I-PER
troops O

that O
German B-MISC
next O

in O
Bosnia B-LOC

current O
NATO-led B-MISC
) O

( O
IFOR B-ORG
is O

in O
Bosnia B-LOC

But O
Ruehe B-PER
am I-ORG

told O
Bild B-ORG
am I-ORG
Sonntag I-ORG

( O
Bosnian B-MISC

, O
Ruehe B-PER

a O
NATO B-ORG

former O
Yugoslavia B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SunGard B-ORG
unit O

buy O
CheckFree B-ORG

BEGIN_TAG O
SAN B-LOC
MATEO I-LOC
1996-08-23 O

, O
Calif. B-LOC

BEGIN_TAG O
SunGard B-ORG
Shareholder I-ORG
Systems I-ORG
Inc I-ORG
Data I-ORG
